字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
归我咯
Give me that!
滚开
Move!
先生 先生 给我回来
Hey, sir! Sir! Come back!
我得走了
I've gotta get outta here.
喂喂喂慢着
Boo, boo, boo, hey, hey, hey.
妹子 你带那张清单了吗？
Girl, you got that list of questions?
带辣
Yes.
我觉着我准备充足了
I think I have everything that I need.
你真该庆幸你没感染衣原体
Be happy you ain't got this chlamydia, all right?
哦 妹子 我之前试着尿尿来着
Ooh, girl, I tried to take a piss earlier,
尼玛感觉像有条恶龙在我逼里喷火啊
it was like there was an angry dragon inside my snatch,
你造吗 《权力的游戏》里那种龙啊
you know, like some Game of Thrones shit!
那真可怕 卡提莎
That's terrible, Kateesha.
但每次高大帅的壮哥哥来蹭我这肥臀
I can't help it when a tall, athletic brother
我就忍不住咯
come pushing up on this thickness.
耶 啊疼
Ooh, yeah... Oh, shit!
天啊妹子 我他妈每一天都在庆幸
Oh, God, girl, I thank God every motherfucking day
“超音速”小哥搬去俄州了
that the SuperSonics moved to Oklahoma. Shit.
好吧 我真得走了 不然要赶不上你的采访
Okay, I'm gonna go so I won't be late for your interview.
你他妈穿的啥啊？
What the fuck are you wearing, girl?
没有迷彩 没有网袜 连一点糖果色都没有？
There ain't no camouflage, no fishnets and no fluorescent colors.
你觉得你躲在暗处有人能看到你吗 小婊咂？
How they gonna see you in the dark, bitch? How they gonna see you?
我真的得走了
I gotta go.
真气派
Wow, so big.
哦 不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
你要是在找流浪汉之家的话 你得下两层楼
If you're looking for the homeless shelter, it's two doors down.
不…不是的 我是汉娜・斯蒂尔
Oh, no, I'm... I'm Hannah Steale.
我来见布莱克先生
I'm here to see Mr. Black.
你就是那个大学生妹子啊 外套给我吧？
The college bitch. May I take your coat?
好 谢谢你
Yes, please. Thank you.
恶…
Ew...
跟我来
Follow me.
温馨提示
In case you're wondering,
我就是操过老板的性感小秘书
I'm the hot secretary who's fucking the boss,
意思就是说 你这种新来的蠢萌实习生没机会的
which means there's no room for the dopey intern
更何况你这一头油毛和肥大腿
with the damaged hair and the cankles.
过来
Come here.
呃
Ugh!
他吃完午饭 打完壁球后…
That's the smell of his balls...
…的蛋蛋就是这个味道
...after lunch and two games of racquetball.
嗯…
Mmm...
祝你一天愉快 斯蒂尔小姐
Have a nice day, Ms. Steale.
屁股平平小婊咂
Plain-ass bitch.
啊 我的脖子 疼 哦
Ow! My neck. Ow. Ooh.
你…
You...
噢噢噢噢卧槽
Oh, shit!
我刚才应该刹车的
I guess I should've tried pulling.
卡文海尔纳小姐
Ms. Kavahellnah.
我是克里斯蒂安・布莱克
Christian Black.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
啊 我觉得没事
I think so, yeah.
很好 因为你他妈糟透辣
Good, 'cause you got fucked up!
我是说 你跟头发疯犀牛一样撞上那个雕塑
I mean, you hit that statue like a hard-charging rhino,
我之所以说犀牛是因为你真是够肥的
and I say rhino because you're a lot fatter than I thought,
而且你鼻子上那个痘痘 看起来就像是个小犀牛角
and you got this bump on your nose that resembles a small horn.
- 要不你还是挤掉吧  - 好的
- Maybe you wanna get that squeezed. - Okay.
对付痘痘就得主动出击
A little Proactive on it.
我不是什么卡文海尔纳
I'm not Ms. Kavahellnah.
你不是卡文海尔纳？
You ain't Ms. Kavahellnah?
- 那你他妈是谁？ - 我叫汉娜・斯蒂尔
- Who the fuck are you? - My name is Hannah Steale.
我和卡提莎
I'm studying literature
都是文学系的大学生
with Kateesha at the university.
欧
Oh.
那请坐
Please, have a seat.
- 谢谢  - 别客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
不是
No.
- 不是  - 那你要啥啊？
- No. - So, what do you want?
老天 直接说出来
Jesus Christ! Just spit it out!
铅笔
A pencil.
铅笔…你怎么不早说
A pencil...You should've just said that in the beginning!
老天 给 拿去
Gosh! Here, take 'em!
- 老天爷  - 谢谢你
- Jesus! - Thank you.
你最好给我打起精神来 斯蒂尔小姐
You gotta get your shit together, Ms. Steale.
操…
Shit...
这些是卡提莎写的问题
These are Kateesha's questions, okay?
“你有很多钱”
"You have mad stacks of cash."
“你怎么挣到的 能不能分我一点”
"How'd you get it, and can I get some?"
哦…斯蒂尔小姐
Oh...Ms. Steale.
我挣钱的法子
I got my money
和大多数黑人企业家一样
the way most black entrepreneurs got theirs.
- 房地产？ - 贩毒啦
- Real estate? - Drug dealing.
瞧 你首先得把整件事了解清楚
See, you have to know your business inside and out.
我吸过一阵子可卡因 没吸多久
I smoked crack. Not for long,
刚好吸到我知道鸡鸡尝起来什么味
but just long enough to know what a penis tastes like.
味道和烤牛臀差不多
Tastes like raw rump roast.
- 嗯  - 恶
- Mmm. - Ew!
我当时全身发灰 像个外星人一样
I got all ashy, like E.T. when he was sick in the river.
掉了六颗牙
I lost six essential teeth.
你有没有试过只用一颗臼齿吃牛排？
Have you ever tried to eat steak with one molar?
没 我干嘛要那样？
No. Why would I do that?
边吸边啃
Gnaw and suck.
一点点边吸边啃 很痛苦的
Gnaw and suck. It's hard.
- 那你熬过来大概是幸运吧  - 不
- Could be that you're lucky. - No.
[美国演员]
基努・里维斯才幸运
Keanu Reeves is lucky.
[美国嘻哈歌手]
弗罗・里达才幸运
Flo Rida is lucky.
[澳大利亚饶舌歌手]
伊基・阿塞利亚才幸运
Iggy Azalea is lucky.
是啊 他真幸运
Yeah, he's lucky.
那下个问题
Next question.
“你是有点基 还是他妈基到爆炸？”
"Is you gay, or is you gay as a motherfucker?"
你摸过别人鸡鸡并不能代表你是基佬
Just because you touch a penis doesn't mean you're gay.
尤其是为了钱或者可卡因
Especially if it's for money or crack.
只有你喜欢去摸别人鸡鸡才能说明你是基佬
You're only gay if you enjoy touching penis.
我摸别人鸡鸡的时候想着…“老子不喜欢这么干”
You touch a penis with attitude, like..."I don't really like this."
那不能被称作基 而是有探索精神
That ain't gay. It's just exploratory.
我记得你说你主修英语
You said you're an English major.
[分别为英国文学之父、英国浪漫主义诗人和英国诗作家]
那你是因为乔叟 雪莱还是济慈的作品
Was it Chaucer, Shelley or Keats
才爱上文学的呢？
that first made you fall in love with literature?
[美国儿童文学家]
- 是苏斯  - 苏斯啊
- It was Seuss. - Seuss!
-“ 戴帽子的猫 小孩一号和小孩二号” -“ …和小孩二号”
- "Cat in the Hat, Thing 1 and Thing 2." - "...and Thing 2!"
谁不想当那俩娃啊？
I mean, who doesn't wanna be them?
告诉你 今年万圣节 我和我弟弟
Well, you know, me and my brother were Thing 1
就打扮成了他们俩
and Thing 2 for Halloween this year.
- 真的？ - 是啊 你看
- Really? - Yeah. Check this out.
啊天呐 看看你们俩
Oh, my God, look at both of you!
我们自称逼崽子一号和逼崽子二号
We called 'em Thang 1 and Thang 2.
真有意思
That's amazing.
如果我想雇你怎么办？
What if I wanted to hire you?
不好说 我看到那些打扮妖艳的女人
I don't know. I see the way the women dress around here.
我觉得这儿并不适合我
I don't exactly fit in.
你看 除了你那low逼毛衣
You know, despite the Salvation Army sweater,
油光发亮的头毛
the greasy weaves,
还有你那个比亚瑟小子都大的鼻子
and your big ol' Usher nose,
你居然有种反常的美感
there's something oddly attractive about you.
恩 你就是个小丑逼
Yeah, you're like the little ugly runt
在一堆可爱小狗中间的小丑逼
in a litter full of pretty puppies.
那种没人愿意摸的丑逼小狗
You know, the little ugly one that nobody wants to touch.
没毛大眼 长相狂野的丑逼小狗
You're, all hairless and big-eyed and wild-looking.
但就是让人想带回家 好好爱抚一番
But you just wanna take you home and give you love,
或者把你捆上石头
or stuff you in a sack with a bunch of rocks
直接沉大海
and just toss your little ugly ass at the bottom of the ocean.
了结你的痛苦
Just put you out your misery.
欧 行
Oh. Okay.
谢谢你 布莱克先生
Thank you, Mr. Black.
别 叫我克里斯蒂安就好
Please, call me Christian.
- 克里斯蒂安  - 我希望我回答了你的所有问题
- Christian. - I hope I answered all your questions.
你是回答了啊
You certainly did.
- 汉娜  - 克里斯蒂安
- Hannah. - Christian.
哦卧槽
Ooh, shit!
啊老天
Oh, God!
啊
Oh!
老天啊
Jesus Christ!
老天 快让它停下
Oh, God, make it stop!
白人姑娘 去把那电梯给老子修好
White girls, get that elevator fixed.
哦 汉娜
Ooh, Hannah!
那么 他咋样啊
So, how was he?
还不错吧 我觉得
He was all right, I guess.
哦卧槽 你把他上了 我就知道
Oh, shit! You fucked him, girl! I knew that shit!
恩 搞那个丁丁 搞那个丁丁
Yeah, girl, get that dick, girl, get that dick.
怎么样 搞那个丁丁 耶
What? Uh! Get that dick! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
在城中心 操你妈的搞那个丁丁
Take it to town, motherfucker. Get that dick.
欧耶欧耶
Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
操你妈欧耶
Shit, girl, yeah! Ooh!
咋样 他丁丁大不
So, did he have a big dick?
- 啥？ - 咋 很细吗
- What? - Ooh, girl, was it like real skinny, girl,
- 还是又细又长那种啊？
or was it like real long, like skinny long?
那样的话他丁丁就比较奇葩了
'Cause that's fucking weird.
还是 短又粗呢妹子
But, like, short and thick, girl?
短又粗的丁丁我还能忍
I can get down with that short, fat dick.
跟…跟丁丁压根没关系
No, there is... There's no...There's no dick.
你有没有记住我说的话啊？
Remember what I told you, okay?
如果他丁丁头上有红色小点点
If it's got like little red zit-like things on the head of that shit,
你就只能和他肛X
you put that in your butt, okay?
他可能会说“哦妹子没事的 只是赘皮啦”
He gonna be like, "Oh, girl, no, it's just skin tags."
可是你他妈鸡鸡上能长多少赘皮啊？
Bitch, you got 47 skin tags on your dick?
这种鬼话骗不到我
I ain't falling for that shit.
或者说再也骗不到我了 明白？
"Again!" Okay?
恩 但是你得承认 他简直帅爆了
Mmm, but you gotta admit, girl, he is bangin'! Mmm!
是啊 如果你喜欢那种超级成功
Yeah, I guess if you're into the wildly-successful,
超级帅气 还可能有点儿危险的人
super-handsome, possibly-dangerous thing,
那克里斯蒂安・布莱克就是你的菜
then Christian Black is your guy.
妹子 我在说李尔・韦恩诶
Bitch, I'm talkin' 'bout Lil Weezy!
哦 脏辫加纹身哟
Ooh, girl, he got tats on his tats.
他根本就不怕把女人肚子搞大
And he ain't afraid to get a bitch pregnant.
他就把宝宝甩给你然后啥都不管
Let you keep the baby and everythin'.
真棒
Mmm.
你要吃那个吗？
You gonna eat that?
嘿嘿 我希望能找到个这尺寸的男人
Ooh, I wish I could find a man the size of this to satisfy me.
希望这坨玩意儿最好不含谷蛋白
This shit better be gluten-free.
恩 布莱克先生
Hmm, Mr. Black.
啊天呐
Oh, God.
恩…天呐 克里斯蒂安
Mmm... God, Christian.
恩…
Mmm...
哦老天 你知道我想干啥
Oh, my God, you know what I wanna do.
- 你好  - 我操？
- Hi. - What the fuck?
巧遇啊 斯蒂尔小姐
What a pleasant surprise, Ms. Steale.
别 叫我汉娜就行了
Please, call me Hannah.
好吧 斯蒂尔小姐
Okay, Ms. Steale.
我只是来这买点东西
I was just in the area and wanted to pick up a few items.
你在跟踪我吗 布莱克先生
Are you stalking me, Mr. Black?
是啊
Yes.
除非你不喜欢我跟着你
I mean, unless you don't want me to.
可你喜欢 对吧？
You do want me to, don't you?
仔细想想咯
Just something to think about.
你要买点啥？
Can I help you with something?
恩
Yes.
我要买线缆带和胶布
I would like to pick up some cable ties and some tape.
那你运气不错 我这刚好有线缆带
Well, you're in luck, we got some cable ties right here.
- 你要什么颜色的？ - 红色
- What color do you want? - Red.
激情的颜色
The color of passion.
胶布在这边 跟我来吧
The tape is this way. Follow me.
如果我不认识你的话
If I didn't know better,
我可能会把你当做连环杀手啥的
I might mistake you for a serial killer.
别扯淡了 如果我是连环杀手
Don't be ridiculous. If I was a serial killer,
我就要用到绳子 斧头 碱液 氨水
I'd need rope, ax, lye, ammonia,
绿素 刨片机 塑料布
chlorophyll, wood chipper, plastic sheets
和三大箱帮宝适尿裤
and three large boxes of space Pampers.
和一把铲子
And a shovel.
我刚刚一想…
Second thought...
我觉得我还要再买些东西
I think I need to pick up a few more items.
那 这些就是你要的咯
Well, looks like you're all set now.
谢谢 斯蒂尔小姐
Thank you, Ms. Steale.
嘿 如果你的室友需要为那些调查问题拍照的话
Hey, if your roommate needs a photo to go with the story,
我明天就在 后天也在
I'll be around tomorrow. And the next day.
大后天还在
And the day after that.
其实这一周都在
I'm actually around all of next week.
来 打我电话就行
Here. Just contact me.
“克里斯蒂安・布莱克”
"Christian Black."
“我不是个男生意人 我是个有生意的…男人”
"I'm not a bidness man, I'm a bidness... man."
谢谢你的帮助啦 斯蒂尔小姐
Thank you so much for your help, Ms. Steale.
帮宝适到货了记得通知我
Let me know when those space Pampers come in, okay?
给我留三箱
Save me three boxes!
我得推这车走好一段路
Got a long drive ahead of me.
拜拜
Bye!
我会打给你的
I'm gonna call you.
- 杰西  - 嗨
- Jesse! - Hey.
谢谢你赶在最后关头帮我
Thank you so much for doing this last minute.
汉娜 你是我最好的朋友
Hannah, listen, you are my best friend, okay?
我为你做什么都可以 明白？
You know I'd do anything for you, right?
哦~
Oh!
- 是啊 你要是给我撸一管就更好了  - 啥？
- Yeah. I'd really love a handjob, though. - What?
我说我挺喜欢干这活的 挺有趣
I said I really love this job. It's amazing.
啊天呐 来抱一个
Oh, my God. Get in here.
过会儿我想上了你
Later I wanna hit it.
啊…额…
Uh...Um...
你刚说啥我没听清
I didn't catch the last thing.
我说我过会儿想去酒吧
I said later I wanna hit the bar.
- 哦  - 拜托 汉娜
- Oh. - Come on, Hannah,
柏拉图式友谊就是这么玩儿的
it's what platonic friends do.
明白不？一起喝个酒
You know? You grab a beer, right?
然后啪啪啪
Then you make out and have sex
直到我们开始对友谊产生怀疑 明白？
until we question the status of our friendship or whatever, you know?
- 大概是吧  - 是啊 再抱一个
- I guess. Come on. - Yeah. Come here.
- 哇  - 卧槽
- Whoa! - Whoa!
汉娜 你刚刚是不是亲我的嘴了？
Hannah! Did you just kiss me on my lips?
- 等等 我以为…  - 别 听我说 咱们先把事情说明白
- Wait, I thought that... - No. Listen. Okay, let's get one thing clear.
- 我们只是朋友 别把事情弄尴尬  - 不是 我以为…
- We are just friends. Don't make it weird. - Oh, no, I thought...
- 没关系 我等会儿就操你  - 慢 你说啥？
- It's okay, I'll fuck you later. - Wait. What?
我说等会再见
I said I'll see you later.
- 天啊 汉娜  - 哦
- Jeez, Hannah. - Oh.
走啊
Just go.
嘭 啪
Pow! Pow!
妹子 他现在盯着你
Girl, he's staring at you like some real
盯的巨他妈认真
Fear-type shit right now, girl.
他看起来就像是
He look like Marky Mark
刚刚离开节奏帮乐队开始演戏的马克・沃尔伯格
after he left the Funky Bunch and started acting, girl.
好 来微笑一个
All right, give me a smile.
茄子
Cheese.
好 你他妈再也不要微笑了 好吗？
All right, don't ever fucking smile again, okay?
他约我拍完照一起去喝咖啡
He asked me to go to coffee with him after the shoot.
哟 真温馨
Oh, girl, that's cute!
上次我喝咖啡
Last time I went to coffee,
是我去吃麦当劳的时候啦
I got eaten out outside of McDonald's.
那菜单看得我高潮迭起
That McCafé menu got a girl gushin'.
好 让我们来轰炸全网
All right, let's break the Internet.
吃啊
Eat.
我又不是你的狗 别对我指手画脚的
I'm not your dog, you can't tell me what to do.
是啊 如果你是我的狗 我会这么做
You're right. If you were my dog, I would do this.
坏姑娘 坏姑娘 坏坏坏坏姑娘
Bad girl! Bad, bad, bad girl!
好 那么跟我聊聊你的家庭吧
So, tell me about your family.
恩…
Well...
我老爹在我两岁的时候就把我抛弃了
My dad left me when I was two years old,
所以我基本是本我的养父 罗恩养大的
so I was mostly raised by my stepdad, Ron.
真尼玛逼没意思
That's painfully uninteresting.
你老妈呢？
How about your mother?
- 她结过八次婚了  - 恩
- She's been married eight times. - Yeah.
她是个无药可救的浪漫主义者
She's an incurable romantic.
你是浪漫主义者吗？
Are you a romantic?
我觉得是吧
I guess.
我是说 我喜欢在海滩上散步
I mean, I like long walks on the beach.
我喜欢学宝宝说话 喜欢两人依偎在一起
I like baby talk, I like to cuddle.
[美国畅销小说作家]
哦 我超爱尼古拉斯・斯派克斯的电影
Ooh, and I love Nicholas Sparks movies.
[美国女演员、歌手]
包括麦莉・塞勒斯那部？
Even the one with Miley Cyrus?
- 那是我最爱呢  - 拜拜傻逼
- That's my favorite one! - Bitch, I'm out!
- 干杯  - 恩
- Cheers. - Yeah.
啊这酒喝起来就像是我春假上过的一个白人男仔
Ooh, that tastes like a white boy on spring break.
我恨他 但是我要打给他
I hate him. I'm gonna call him.
再来一杯吗？
You want another drink?
恩 喝醉了就忘了
Yes. Drink to forget.
没错儿
Yeah.
恩没错
Oh, yeah.
这也太难喝了
That tastes horrible.
莫莉应该没把药完全搅碎
The Molly must not be crushed up all the way.
我来帮你
Let me fix it for you.
我要去下厕所
I gotta go to the bathroom.
你要干嘛？
You gotta what?
我要去厕所
I gotta go to the ladies' room.
- 啥？ - 老娘要去拉屎
- Huh? - I have to take a shit!
汉娜…汉娜 你还好吗？有点头晕？
Hannah... Hannah, you feeling all right? A little woozy perhaps?
- 哇  - 怎么？想不清楚事情吗？
- Whoa! - Huh? Unable to make good decisions?
我们应该继续下去 然后你就 恩 给我口X
We should take it to the next level and you, like, suck my dick.
宝贝儿 我们只要继续你就不会难受了 好吗？
Baby, you take it to the next level, you stop feelin' sick, okay?
哦老天 你真是我最好的盆友
Oh, my God. You are my bestest friend.
是啊 能爽到的那种
Yes. With benefits.
啊…用你的手指操我嘴吧
Ah...Fuck my mouth with your fingers.
干
Fuck!
老子操不到了
I'm never gonna get none.
你可以操我啊 我可能不会有多享受 但是你可以操我
I'll fuck you. I ain't gonna like it, but I'll do it.
听着 我不操白人姑娘 明白？
Listen, I don't fuck white girls, okay?
黑鬼 你说谁白？
Nigga, who you callin' white?
她刚才叫我黑鬼…？
She just call me the N word?
搞得我有点性趣盎然啊
Kind of turned me on.
再叫我一次黑鬼
Call me "nigga" again.
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
哟 你好啊
Well, hello there.
恩 我是汉娜
Yeah, this is Hannah.
汉娜 你喝醉了吗
Hannah, are you wasted?
是啊我喝醉了
Yes, I am wasted.
你就一王八蛋 你只资道钱
You're a hole-ass, you're might on the roney,
你则个吸鸡鸡的
you penis suck of yours.
你说话有点深奥 听着 我要你现在就回家
You sound like Yoda. Listen, I want you to go home right now.
憋对劳资指手画脚
Don't tell me what to do,
先叫我去喝咖灰
Mr. "Oh, let's go for coffee.
又粗鲁待我的混蛋
"No, stay away from me!"
这样吧 我用你能听懂的话说
Let me put this in words you can understand.
尼现在赶紧给劳资肥家
Now, right home you go!
不
No!
我告诉他辣
I told him.
- 嗯哼  - 傻逼你好臭啊
- Mmm-hmm. - Bitch, you smell like shit.
恶
Ugh!
哦 汉娜 汉娜 外面很冷诶
Oh, Hannah! Hannah! Hey, it's cold out here.
你穿这样怎么能出来
You can't come out like that.
哦 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
你感觉怎么样
How you feelin'?
有点醉
Just a little bit drunk.
你是 像川普想做总统那样醉？
Are you, like, Donald-Trump-running-for-president drunk
还是说 像川普说他讨厌墨西哥人那样醉
or, like, Donald-Trump-saying-he-don't-like-Mexicans drunk?
因为他说的都他么疯话
'Cause that's some crazy shit, man.
很多墨西哥人都在进入美国
A lot of Mexicans out there just crossing the border and shit!
你应该给他们瞧瞧来自黑鬼的爱 黑鬼的爱
And you show them niggas love! Show them niggas love!
我也给你瞧瞧我的爱吧
Can I show you some love?
啥？不要
What? No!
拜托 就亲一个嘛
Come on. Come on! Just one kiss, man!
我都不知道你啥时候还能再这么醉了
I don't know when you gonna be this drunk again!
来嘛 给我亲一个
Come on, gimme that kiss!
啊 停手
Ow! Stop!
- 嘿 她说了停手  - 停手
- Hey! Hey! She said no! - Stop!
克里斯蒂安
Christian!
黑鬼你推我？
You just push me, nigga?
欧你惹上大麻烦了小子
Oh, you got some crazy shit coming, boy.
等等 这黑鬼要还手？
Wait. Hold up. This nigga comin' back?
这就来 黑鬼
Comin' to you, nigga.
他来了
He comin' back!
卧槽
Damn!
你就躺着吧 克里斯蒂安
Christian, stay down!
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
这黑鬼就是个忍者 是个忍者啊
The nigga's a ninja! This nigga's a ninja.
世界巨星呐
Worldstar!
- 傻逼  - 他真帅啊
- Bitch! - He had such a beautiful face.
他走了没
Did he leave?
你最好抓紧逃吧
You better run!
哦 克里斯蒂安 我不太舒服
Oh, I don't feel so good, Christian.
来吧 我送你回家
Come on, let's get you home.
别 我不能和你一起
Oh, no, I can't with you,
我室友还在里面呢
because my roommate is in there.
别担心 有人会照顾好她的
Don't worry. She's being well taken care of.
你叫什么来着
What's your name again?
我叫伊莱
My name is Eli.
[此处恶搞加拿大歌手 The Weekend]
我朋友都叫我 Weekday
My friends call me Weekday.
我是克里斯蒂安的弟弟
I'm Christian's brother.
哦…恩…
Ooh... Mmm...
比较穷的那个
The poor one.
恩恩…
Mmm-mmm...
我懂你的意思
I know what you're saying,
“哦他虽然物质贫穷 可他精神富有”
"Oh, he's financially poor, yet spiritually rich."
恩…
Mmm...
- 不对  - 你感觉到了什么？
- Nah, that don't count. - What do you feel?
- 你感觉到了什么？ - 老天啊
- What do you feel? - Oh, my God.
卧槽这得有多长？
When does that end? Oh, my God!
我鸡鸡太重啦所以从不装钱
The weight of my penis makes my money too heavy to carry around!
耶死
Yes!
再见了 女人
I'll see you later, woman.
- 下次再见  - 我该怎么摸你？
- Until we meet again. - How can I touch you?
我是说 怎么联系你
I mean, get in touch with you!
我的号码
My number
是七
is seven.
哦
Oh!
真是个好数字 老天
That's a good number. Oh, God.
我会打给你的
I'mma call you!
早上好啊
Good morning.
我就这么瞪着你一晚上了
I've been staring at you all night.
眼睛都没眨一下
I haven't blinked once.
尼玛我眼睛疼死了
Gosh, my eyes are hurting.
- 我为什么在这儿？ - 我带你过来的
- How did I get here? - I brought you here, Hannah.
你给我换衣服了？
Did you undress me?
是啊 没错…
I sure did. Mmm...
老天 我们难道…
My God, we didn't...
没 我们没内啥
No, we didn't.
我可以证明 我的蛋蛋都憋青了
And I have the blue balls to prove it.
看啊
Look at these things.
恶
Ugh!
那是啥 卧槽那是啥？
What are those? What the fuck are those?
啊…疼死了
Oh... It hurts so much.
我不知道该咋办啊
I don't know what to do!
你为什么给我看这个？
Why are you showing me this?
我给你准备了早餐
I ordered you some breakfast.
来 吃了吧 你需要吃东西来恢复精神
Here. Eat. You'll need your strength.
可你舔过这个 没准还干过啥其他恶心事儿
But you licked this one, and did all sorts of other weird stuff to it.
能不能给我拿片新的？有果酱吗
Can I get a fresh one? Maybe some jam.
不行 吃
No, eat it.
你为什么不能别再骚扰我了呢 克里斯蒂安？
Why don't you just leave me alone, Christian?
因为我不能留你一人
Because I'm incapable of leaving you alone.
我是个持证的专业尾随痴汉
I'm a certified stalker.
我收到过四条禁止令 并且马上要收到第五条了
I have four restraining orders, and I'm currently working on a fifth.
听我说
Listen to me.
我不懂那些浪漫的事儿
I don't do the romance thing.
肛X 行 拳X 没问题
Anal, yes. Fisting, sure.
双龙探洞 不在话下
Two in the pink, one in the stink, yeah.
这些我懂 但我不懂浪漫
I do that. But I don't do romance.
我真想咬一口你的嘴唇
You know, I'd like to bite that lip.
我也想被你咬
I wish you would.
啊
Ow!
啊 啊…
Ow! Mmm...
啊老天
Oh, my God!
来吧 我送你出去
Come on, let's get you outta here.
- 老天 我都湿了  - 呃
- God, that made me wet. - Oh!
啊好爽
Oh, love it.
放你妈的屁
Fuck the bullshit.
你怎么样？
How you doin'?
眼睛睁开 蜥蜴吻 来
Open your eyes. Lizard kisses, come on.
吸血鬼之咬
Vampire bite!
爽 再来
I love it! More!
好 好
Yes! Yes!
哦老天啊
Oh, my God!
闭嘴乖乖看
You shut up and watch.
滚
Get outta here!
不好意思
Excuse me.
我得警告你 我一进电梯就会变得色色的
I have to warn you, elevators make me horny.
欧爹爹 我想要你给我写首歌
Ooh, Daddy, I want you to write a song about me.
我想做你的女神
I wanna be your muse.
恩 时机正好
Oh, this is a great time.
我现在灵感正旺
I'm inspired to write a song
要写你收关于你的歌
about you right now.
啊好爽
Ooh, that feels so good.
因为我喜欢不戴套
'Cause I love havin' sex unprotected
哦
Ooh.
我喜欢上裸体的你
And I love when my dick's in you naked
再深一点 再深一点
Deeper, Daddy, deeper! Yeah!
对你野性全开 哟哟哟
Goin' raw in you, you, you...
爽 爽
Yes! Yes!
对你野性全开 哟哟哟哟
Goin' raw in you, you, you, you
哦 我觉得你这歌都能拿白金唱片了
Ooh, I think you going platinum in about two minutes! Oh!
你被感染了哟
You're infected, yeah
需要杀杀菌咯
Need antiseptic, yeah
因为妹子你热情似火哟
'Cause, girl, you burned it
哦这一句是E小调吗
Ooh, that like an E minor or something?
热情似火哟
Oh, you burned it!
Oh, you burned
啊…你…
Ah...You...
啊卧槽
Ooh, shit.
卧槽
Motherfucker!
你搞完没？我要去教堂了
You done? I gotta get to church.
- 嗨  - 哦
- Hey! - Oh.
你们俩在搞啊
You two are fucking.
- 哦  - 嗨兄弟
- Ooh. - Hey, bro.
- 你怎么样啊？ - 我的兄弟
- How you doin'? - My brother.
哥哥 我过得平静又安逸
My brother, peace and blessings.
汉娜 这是我小弟弟 伊莱
Hannah, this is my little brother, Eli.
- 小？ - 是啊
- Little? - Yes.
我是伊莱 就像那些根据书改编的电影
I'm Eli, like the movie about the book,
很“深”奥
because I'm deep.
他确实很“深”奥
He is deep.
蛋蛋“深”奥
Balls deep.
没错儿
Yeah.
卡提莎和我提到过你
Kateesha told me a lot about you.
你…呃 你
Yeah, you're like... You're, like, a lot
比我想象的身材要差许多
plainer than I thought you would be.
恩 她身材不好 但是很漂亮
Well, she plain but pretty.
- 你就像是一面砖墙 无聊又死板…  - 好了
- You're like a brick wall, just boring and rigid... - Okay.
还有点儿阴郁
And just ashy in some places.
好了好了好了 闲话说够了
Okay, okay, okay, okay, enough with the small talk.
我们还有很长的路要赶
We have a long drive ahead of us.
是啊 很高兴遇见你
We do. Great pleasure. It's been a pleasure.
月亮会再度升起的
The moon shall rise again.
哦哦 真浪漫 什么意思呢
Ooh, that so romantic, boo. What that mean?
- 再见辣 傻逼  - 好 明白了 等会儿见
- Deuces, bitch. - Okay, I got you! I see you later!
- 很高兴见到你  - 再见
- Nice meeting you. - Bye.
好了 听我说 一会儿来办公室找我
All right, so listen. Meet me at the office later.
我给你准备了些特殊的东西
I have something special planned for you.
- 好吗？再见傻逼 嗯哼
- Okay? Deuces, bitch. - Mmm-hmm.
- 你他妈叫谁傻逼？ - 啊卧槽
- Who you calling a bitch? - Oh, shit!
该死 妹子
Damn, girl.
我就是说说 他对她那么说了
I was just saying. He said it to her,
我以为那样挺浪漫
and I thought it was cute.
恩
Mmm.
该死 傻逼…我说 妹子
Damn, bitch... I mean, girl.
准备好去坐耪ㄌ斓淖骑了吗
Are you ready for the ride of your life?
天啊 我们要去坐直升机了吗？
Oh, my God! Are we gonna go in your helicopter?
我真不敢相信你居然以为我要带你去坐直升机
I can't believe you thought I was gonna take you on the chopper.
我们都还没上过床呢
We haven't even fucked yet.
你先请
After you.
我了个操 这是你家啊？
Holy shit! You live here?
怎么 黑人就不能住这种好房子了？
What, a black man can't have a nice place like this?
不能 一个黑人是住不起这样的好房子
No, a black man cannot have a beautiful place like this.
[美国黑人男演员]
你知道 韦斯利・斯奈普斯曾经也住过这种豪宅
You know, Wesley Snipes had a place like this,
后来他开始交税了
before he stopped doing his own taxes.
来点酒吗？
How about some wine?
好啊 谢谢
Yes, please.
好
Okay.
你知道我为什么带你来我家吗 汉娜
Do you know why I brought you here, Hannah?
我猜是要来一场甜蜜的嘿咻
I'm assuming to make sweet love.
我不嘿咻 我操死你
I don't make love. I fuck.
又狠又快
Hard and quick.
非常快
Really quick.
[美国女子柔道运动员]
和龙达・露西打拳一样 一眨眼就结束
It's like a Ronda Rousey fight. You blink and it's over.
好吧
Okay.
但首先 你得签一个保密合约
But first you're gonna have to sign
保密合约
a nondisclosure agreement.
那是啥？
What's that?
大概意思就是“嘴闭紧保平安”
It's basically lawyer talk for "shut the fuck up."
来吧 我会和你解释的
Come with me. I'll explain.
保密合约
A nondisclosure agreement
能同时保护我们俩 但主要是保护我
protects both you and me, but mostly me.
这扇门背后是我的游乐场
Behind this door is my playroom.
你指游戏机那种游乐场吗？
You mean, like, for your PlayStation and stuff?
哟钥匙真好看
Ooh. That's a nice key.
好紧
So tight.
钥匙孔你不想开啊 你准备好了吗
Keyhole don't wanna open! You ready to get opened?
上弹啊兄弟 我早就说了上弹
Reload, man! Reload! I told you to reload!
我超爱玩叉烧盒子
I'm an Xbox man myself.
下一轮该你了 布莱克
Oh, you next, Black!
你不会想要我来虐你的
You don't want none of this.
你搞完那个女同学
Yo, when you done with Wendy Williams over there,
就过来玩 老子揍扁你
jump on this game so I can shoot you in the face!
我跟你实话实说 克里斯蒂安 这女人一点儿也不漂亮
I'm gonna be honest with you, Christian. She's not attractive.
她看起来像得了狼疮
Like, the bitch look like she got lupus.
欧 你看起来像刚从别人屁眼里拔出来的大拇指
Well, you look like a thumb that's been yanked out of somebody's asshole.
哦~~~
Oh~~~
大绝杀
Slam dunk!
真是疯了 真是疯了
That's crazy. That's crazy.
好吧 那你觉得…
Yeah, well, how about... Ha!
- 我想不出来了  - 因为老娘比你
- I got nothing. - 'Cause I'm better than you.
好了 我有些东西
Okay, well, I got something
很想给你看看
I really wanna show you.
啊老天 不会又是一群傻逼老黑吧
Oh, my God. It's not more broke niggas, is it?
- 当然不是  - 无意冒犯
- No more broke niggas. - No offense.
别担心你鸡鸡内生长的阴毛
And don't worry about those ingrown hairs on your penis.
隔着裤子别人看不见
We can't see them through your pants.
别跟她认真 老兄
Don't give her all the dick, bro.
- 她不配  - 操一半就好啦
- She don't deserve it. - Half the dick.
那女人骂起你来简直飞天
Over there fucking Charles Barkley.
我操你妈 拜拜
Fuck this shit! I'm out!
拜托 斯蒂尔小姐 别这么老顽固
Please, Ms. Steale. Just keep an open mind.
挑逗用具
Tantalizing.
这是我奶奶传下来的
Got these from my grandma.
你真他妈变态
You're a sick motherfucker.
[美国演员，曾下药并强奸过三十五名女性]
不 比尔・科斯比才是变态
No, Bill Cosby's a sick motherfucker.
我只是与众不同而已
I'm just a dominant.
那跟我有什么关系？
What does that have to do with me?
我想要你通过性的方式把自己交给我
I want you to give yourself to me sexually.
所以才有那些鞭子 锁链 吓人的性玩具
Hence all the whips, chains and freaky sex toys.
那我又能得到什么呢？
And what would I get out of it?
老子啊
Me.
哦老天呐
Oh, my God!
- 呃 让我先想清楚  - 嗯哼
- Ooh. Let me get this straight. - Mmm-hmm.
所以你想用那些东西鞭打我…
So, you wanna beat me with these paddles...
- 鞭子  - 好多鞭子
- Whip. - Whips.
你想把我锁在这个架子上…
You wanna chain me to this rack...
诶…手铐
Eh...Handcuff.
然后用丧尽天良的办法羞辱我
And humiliate me in unimaginable ways,
作为交换
and in exchange for all this torture,
我就能得到你？
I get you?
一点儿没错
Yeah, that's correct.
这世上有女人愿意这么做？
And women go for this?
有一些辣
Some women.
- 这就像是成年人的迪士尼  - 没错儿
- It's like Disneyland for grown-ups. - Yeah.
所以 你怎么想？
So, what do you think?
我其实啥都能接受啊
I'm pretty much cool with anything,
只要你别告诉我爹我上了个黑人
as long as you promise you won't tell my dad I fucked a black guy.
你怎么想？
So, what do you think?
两件事 杯子在哪
Two things. Where's the cup,
我们何时能吃屎？
and when do we eat shit?
我们要在这干嘛？
What we supposed to do in here?
恩 我觉得我们应该从玩儿绳子开始
Well, I thought we'd start with a little bit of rope play.
不
No!
好吧 那要不直接上那边的架子 我骑你？
Okay, well, how about I just mount you to that rack over there and spank you?
骑你妈的拐弯屁
Hell to the no!
那鞭打怎么样？
Perhaps a little bit of flogging?
我都不知道你说的鞭打是什么意思
I don't even know what the hell flogging means,
所以打你妈的拐弯屁
so fuck to the no!
好吧 那你说我们该在这干嘛？
Okay, well, what are we supposed to do then?
你给老娘去见耶稣 你就该干这个
You need to find Jesus! That's what you can do.
好 现在情况是这样
Okay, here's how it goes.
我起草了一份标准合同 包含一些基础条目
I've drafted a standard contract that lays out the terms.
很多XX 我们还有更多XX
Lots of sex, we have more sex.
嘿咻嘿咻 我们以XX结束
Yadda-yadda, we end with sex.
你看一下 再跟我说说你想怎么样
You look it over, and you negotiate what you're willing to do.
我知道这么说
I hate to throw a monkey wrench
帮不上什么忙
into the whole works here,
但是我…
but I...
你没什么自信？
You have low self-esteem?
不是的 我…
No. I...
你有恋父情结
You have daddy issues.
不是
No.
我想说的是 我是…
What I'm trying to tell you is, I'm a...
- 处女？ - 没错
- A virgin? - Yeah.
卧槽 不敢相信
Man! I can't believe this!
我不明白
I don't understand!
好吧 你应该至少做过些啥吧
Okay, tell me you've done something.
口X？
Blowjob?
- 口X是X哪里啊？ - 手指爆X？
- Where does the blowing come in? - Finger pop?
- 没  - 没玩过愤怒的熊猫？
- No. - Angry panda?
- 他为什么要愤怒？ - 你为什么这么问？
- Why is it angry? - Why did you ask that?
我的天 好吧 你好歹应该肛X过了吧
Oh, my God! Okay, tell me you've done anal.
我了解这个
I know how it goes.
你让男人X你屁眼
You let guys put it in your little rusty bullet hole
这样你还是可以跟你妈妈或者牧师说你是处女
so you can tell your mama and your pastor that you're still a virgin.
我只是在等
I've just been waiting.
等什么？
For what?
妹子 你都二十好几了
Girl, you are 20-something years old!
这个又不是越酿越香 时间太久会坏掉的
It don't get no better. It's going to spoil!
然后就只能怀小孩了 只能怀小孩 明白？
It's fermenting down there. Just fermenting. Okay?
你告诉我 为什么没人X你
You gonna tell me nobody wanted the pussy?
恩 我对于X对象很挑剔的…
Well, I just am very selective about who I've wanted to...
挑剔？
Oh, selective?
这话听着像是一个没人要的丑婆子说的
Oh, that sound like something somebody with a pussy that nobody wanted would say.
- 喂  - 别会错意
- Hey. - Don't get me wrong.
我也不想去搞黑木耳
I don't want it all worn out like an old washing machine belt
她们的逼要么跟挂在车外的湿垫子一样没劲
or hanging like wet straps in a car wash
要么pia来pia去像个充气床垫
or flapping around like an inflatable figure outside of a mattress store.
但是你至少要有些经验
But I want it to have some experience.
好吧 这样
Okay, look.
我们现在就解决这个问题
We're gonna fix this situation. Right now.
我等这一刻等了一辈子了
I've been waiting my whole life for this.
来吧
Come on.
好
Yes!
呃…这很…
Oh...Very...
很有野人风范嘛
Very Sasquatch of you.
你从没和处女搞过吗？
Have you never had sex with a virgin before?
没和你这么有毛的处女搞过
Not a hairy one.
啊 你划到我了
Ow! You nicked me!
嘘…
Shh...
卧槽？
What the hell?
啊 对了 我肚脐眼外突
Oh, yeah, I have an outie.
哦 哇
Oh, wow!
哦
Whoa!
这尼玛逼还挺有味
That got flavor!
- 搞毛？ - 你是第一个看见我肚脐的人
- What? - You're the first person who's seen it.
来一发爱斯基摩热吻？
Little Eskimo kisses?
哦 还从没人对我这么做过
Ooh, I never had anyone do that to it before.
- 哦 你的牙  - 对不起
- Ooh! Watch the teeth! - Sorry.
中招辣
Got him.
好吧
Okay.
对不起 我没什么时间洗澡
Sorry. I didn't have time to shower.
我操
Shit!
谢谢
Thank you.
哦
Ooh!
好 准备好了吗
Okay. You ready?
老子要带你一飞冲天辣
I'm gonna take youto a whole 'nother galaxy!
啊我操老子要射了
Oh, my God, I'm coming!
啊老天
Oh, God!
天啊天啊天啊天啊
God! God! God! God!
- 哦  - 结束了？
- Whoo! - Already?
啊真爽呀
Oh, that was amazing.
讲真？我居然还期待些
Really? I guess I was expecting something
不同的东西
different.
没关系 这是你第一次 没事的
Don't worry about it. It's your first time. Don't sweat it.
经验丰富了就好了 继续努力
You'll get better with experience. Just keep working on it.
你知道自古以来
Oh, you know, it's customary for a woman
女人都要在事后给男人做一个超大三明治
to make a man an oversized sandwich
来帮助男人恢复精神的对吧
to help him regain his strength.
要么吃剩的披萨也行 或者煎饼果子
Either that or some leftover pizza,or maybe a Hot Pocket.
你想要我现在给你做煎饼果子？
You want me to make you a Hot Pocket now?
这又不是我规定的 我只是在告诉你而已
I don't make the rules, I'm just telling you.
前路漫漫啊孩子
You got a lot to learn, kid.
恩…
Mmm...
你他妈就睡着了？
Are you asleep already?
死黑鬼
Nigga!
呃
Ugh!
克里斯蒂安？
Christian?
- 克里斯蒂安  - 我操
- Christian! - Oh, shit!
那他妈是谁
Who the fuck is that?
我老妈
My mother.
哦
Oh!
真棒
Great.
操 现在我得对付两个疯婊子了
Now I gotta get rid of two crazy bitches. Fuck.
老妈
Mother!
- 啊 克里斯蒂安  - 你好啊
- Ah, Christian. - Hello.
你最好快点换身衣服 我们赛艇会要迟到了
Oh, you better get dressed, or we're gonna be late for the regatta.
我都忘了 就是今天啊
I forgot that was today.
你不会又在吸毒吧？
You're not doing crack again, are you?
- 没有啊老妈  - 我从来都没让你嗑着药长大
- No, Mother.  - I never raised you that way.
可吸毒却是你们家的通病
However, it is a prominent trait in your genealogical pool.
嗨
Hello.
这是我的领土 这是我的领土
I'm standing my ground! I'm standing my ground!
哦我操
Oh, shit!
老妈 你在干嘛啊？那是汉娜・斯蒂尔
Mother, what're you doing? That's Hannah Steale!
我得给你说多少次啊？黑人的命也很重要的
How many times I gotta tell you? Black lives matter.
来 我扶你起来
Come on, let's get you up.
- 汉娜 这是我老妈 克莱尔  - 哦
- Hannah, this is my mother, Claire. - Oh.
不好意思 汉娜
I am so sorry, Hannah.
欧老天 你咪咪真好看
Oh, my, you have beautiful breasts.
我隔着衣服看还以为都下垂了
I would've thought they'd be more droopy,
就像是塞了石头的袜子一样下垂
like a sock with a rock in the toe,
就像寰宇地理杂志里演的那种
like in those National Geographic magazines.
你得理解一下我老妈
You're gonna have to forgive my mother's behavior.
她有时候说疯话 而且还种族歧视
Sometimes she can be factually inaccurate and quite racist.
别为我道歉 克里斯蒂安
Do not apologize for me, Christian.
我是你妈妈 我爱你
I am your mother, and I love you
我把你当做我亲生的白人崽
like you were my own white child.
但是我晚上还是要把钱包藏起来 以防万一
But I still hide my wallet at night, just in case.
你应该这样
As you should, Mother.
很高兴见到你
It is awesome to meet you.
- 你们俩在约会吗？ - 没 我们没在约会
- Are you two dating? - Oh, no, Mother, we're not dating.
我们只是啪啪啪而已
We're just fucking. Hard.
快而狠的啪啪啪 最爽啦
And quick. Apparently, it's the best way.
那好吧 我见到你真的非常高兴 汉娜
Well, I just can't tell you how pleased I am to meet you, Hannah.
我是说 你是我见过克里斯蒂安的第一个女朋友
I mean, you're the first woman I've seen Christian with.
我之前还以为…
I assumed that he was...
欧普拉怎么说的来着？“好好的男生说弯就弯”
What would Oprah say? "On the DL?"
克里斯蒂安 你眼光怎么这么低
Christian, you can do so much better.
哦 老妈
Oh, Mother.
你是世界上最富 最帅的男人之一
You're one of the richest, most handsome men in the world.
你可以去勾搭白妞啊
You could date white women.
[两人分别是高尔夫球星和歌手]
像泰戈尔・伍兹或席尔
Like Tiger Woods and Seal.
好了 我觉得你该走了老妈
Okay, it's time for you to go, Mother.
[分别是演员、音乐制作人、说唱歌手]
或者塔耶・狄格斯 昆西・琼斯？冰老T也行啊
Or like Taye Diggs or Quincy Jones. Or even Ice-T.
汉娜 克里斯蒂安的中国姐姐 梅 来这里啦
Hannah, Christian's Chinese sister, Mai, has come to town,
所以我们准备举办一个家庭晚宴
so we're gonna hide the cats and have the family over for dinner.
- 你也该来啊  - 我跟荣幸
- You should come. - I'd be delighted.
见到你真心很高兴
It was really nice to meet you.
好了真棒 老妈 该走啦
Okay, great. Time to go, Mom.
哦…
Oh...
那我的钱包哪儿去了
Now, where is my wallet?
还在这呐
Still there.
- 你小子永远都猜不到在哪  - 是啊
- You just never know. - Yeah.
恩…
Mmm...
真尼玛好吃
They're delicious. Mmm.
好啦
All right.
早饭吃完了 走吧
We had breakfast. Time to go.
瞧 你的Uber到了咧
Ooh, look, your Uber's here. All right.
好吧 又怎么了？
Okay, what?
说
Spit it out.
恩 你是怎么就喜欢上了
Well, how did you get into this whole
玩儿SM呢
dominant-submissive thing?
我老妈之前有个好朋友
It was one of my mother's really close friends,
还有我的音乐老师
and my music teacher.
我那时十六岁
I was 16.
她比我稍大一点
She was older.
别这么紧张 克里斯蒂安
Don't look so nervous, Christian.
我现在需要你做到最好
All I ask is that you do your very best.
我以为我们是要上音乐课啊
I thought I was supposed to be here for music lessons.
没错啊宝贝儿
Baby, you are.
第一节课从这里开始
And your lesson starts right here.
喂 喂 停
Hey, hey. Ooh. Snap.
[著名黑人AV男星]
你丫简直就像约翰・福尔摩斯啊
We got a regular John Holmes here,
除了没有大丁丁而且秒射
without the big dick and the stamina!
好了 再来 一 二 三
Okay! Again! One, two, three!
啊
Ow!
知道我为什么打你吗 布莱克小子？
Do you know why I hit you in the head with that tambourine, Black?
不知道
I have no idea.
你刚刚节奏是快了还是慢了
Well, were you rushing or were you dragging?
我…我们不是在嘿咻吗
I... I thought I was fucking.
那不算嘿咻
Oh! That wasn't fucking!
现在你来数拍子
Now, count off.
一 二…
One, two...
我是快了还是慢了？
Was I rushing or was I dragging?
- 回到我  - 你快了
- Answer the question! - You were rushing!
哭了？哦 可怜的小崽子
Is that a tear? Oh! Poor little guy.
- 你生气吗？ - 生气
- Are you upset? - I'm upset.
你这个毫无价值的 被领养的 没人爱的小傻逼
You worthless, adopted, unloved little piece of shit!
在我逼里又哭又闹 像个九岁小姑娘一样
Weeping and slobbering over my vagina like a 9-year-old girl!
现在 你他妈最后再说一次
Now, for the last father-fucking time,
- 大声点不然我听不见  - 我生气了
- say it louder so I can hear it! - I'm upset!
哦 布莱克小子 滚下床去 你让老娘恶心
Oh, Black, get off the bed! You make me sick.
- 可我好生气啊  - 滚下床去
- But I'm upset. - Get off the bed!
- 你压根就没准备好  - 我准备好了
- You're not ready for this! - I'm ready!
呃
Ugh!
威利？威利 先一个换你上
Willy? Willy, you're up next.
威利？
Willy?
你最好给老娘打起精神 布莱克小子
You better get your shit together, Black!
你啥都驾驭不了 女人不行音乐也不行
You're not gonna amount to anything, sexually or musically.
而且你知不知道
And you know what the biggest
让我最失望的是什么吗？
disappointment of all is to me?
我以为你们黑人节奏感强鸡鸡也大
I thought all you black men had rhythm and a big dick!
老天 我真是想错了
Boy, was I mistaken!
我节奏感很强的
I have rhythm!
都准备好了 斯蒂尔小姐 这是来自布莱克先生的一点小礼
You're all set, Ms. Steale. Courtesy of Mr. Black.
我操？
What the heck?
那是啥啊？无人机吗？
What is that? Is that a drone?
好了 在这签字就行
All right, just sign here.
谢谢你
Thank you very much.
哟妹子 又给你送礼啦？
Ooh, girl, another gift?
卧槽 你一定把他迷得死去活来
Damn, you must be giving that bomb head!
等下 那是Retina显示屏的Macbook吗？
Wait a minute, is that a Retina display MacBook Pro?
婊咂 你们屁眼交易过了吧
Bitch, you lickin' that butthole!
才没有
I didn't lick a butthole!
卧槽 你真好运啊
Shit, you lucky, girl.
我上周舔过六个屁眼 才拿到一台戴尔啊
Like, I licked six buttholes last week! I got a Dell!
还他妈是台式机
Desktop!
我又不能随身携带
I can't take that shit anywhere, girl.
说到这 又寄东西来了？
Hey, the mail come already?
不是啦
No.
这是克里斯蒂安想让我签的什么嘿咻协议
It's just a weird sex contract Christian wants me to sign.
你签了 就问他要钱 明白不？
You sign that, but then you get that paper, boo, all right?
这是你应得的 继续去舔他屁眼吧
A bitch gotta get hers. You keep licking that bootie, okay?
我们玩儿完了？
We're done?
- 我了个…  - 我看了你发的消息
- Wha... - Yeah, I read your text.
惊讶脸 钻石 便便
Wow face, sparkly diamond, poop?
那表情是啥意思啊卧槽
Like, what does that even mean?
你发的表情搞得我好他妈糊涂啊
You got me all fucked up with your emojis, like...
呃 你怎么钻进去的
Hey, how did you get in here?
这重要吗？
Does it matter?
重要 因为你一不住在这 二没有钥匙
Yes, actually it does matter, because you don't live here and you don't have a key.
你进这篮子又不需要钥匙啊 汉娜
You don't need a key to get in a hamper, Hannah.
好了 现在帮忙把我弄出来
Here, now, help me outta here.
我没藏在你的药柜里算你好运
You're lucky I wasn't in your medicine cabinet,
或者你的首饰盒
or your jewelry box.
我试着藏在你床头柜里来着
I tried to hide in your nightstand,
但是里面放了一本基甸圣经 所以我藏不下了
but you had this Gideon Bible in there and I couldn't fit.
等等 你是破窗进来的吗？
Wait a minute, did you break in through that window?
这扇窗子吗？
This one?
不不不 这可能是任何人干的
Oh, no, that could've been anybody.
地上那块砖头写着“克里斯蒂安的财产”
The brick on the ground says "Property of Christian Black."
“克里斯蒂安…”
"Christian..."
哦 哦 是诶
Yeah, yeah, it does.
但是 那砖头可能属于其他叫克里斯蒂安的黑人的啊 对吧？
But, I mean, that could belong to any black Christian, right?
我是说 闭嘴…
I mean, okay, shh...
不要再问问题了
Enough with the interrogation.
过来
Come here.
别动
Do not move,
不然我就要惩罚你了
or I'll be forced to punish you.
我说了别动
I said don't move!
好
Okay.
哦
Ooh!
毛茸茸的感觉好奇怪 那是啥？
That feels weird. What is that? It's so hairy.
好耶 棒
Yeah! Yes!
慢慢慢慢别动别动别动…
Wait, wait, wait, don't move. Don't, don't...
卧槽啥玩意儿好冰
Damn it, that shit was cold!
你准备好了吗 斯蒂尔小姐？
Are you ready, Ms. Steale?
好了 克里斯蒂安
Yes, Christian.
哦
Ooh!
你带了避孕套的吧？
You brought a condom, right?
- 避孕套？ - 是啊
- A condom? - Yeah.
呃…是啊 当然带了
Oh...Okay. Yeah, of course!
我当然带了避孕套 等我一下
Of course I got a condom. Hold on one second.
操
God damn it!
我就想知道你是不是对我负责
Just knowing you care enough to use protection excites me.
啊哈 俺很值得信赖的
Aha! Old trusty dusty!
一九八二年三月过期 我日？
"March, 1982?" Aw, hell no.
好啦 我找到避孕套了
Yeah, I got one right here! Found it!
来 你听着我打开
Here, let me open it up so you can hear it.
好了
Okay.
我的小兄弟要来辣
I'm just gonna scoot these little bad boys to the side.
啊然后捅这里
Oh! And then I'm gonna park this right there.
哇 感觉好自然哦
Oh, my God, it feels so natural.
感觉你压根没戴套套啊
It's like you're not wearing anything at all!
我这套套是用羊的包皮做的
It's lambskin foreskin.
- 啊 放轻松  - 啥？
- Oh! Just relax. - What?
没 我没和你说话 我在自言自语
No, not you. Now I'm talking to myself.
好了 准备好没
Okay? Oh... Ready?
那可是连续两轮呢
That was like two strokes!
老子可以创世界纪录辣
This nigga's back here settin' records!
老子以后要上广告盒子辣
They gonna put me on a Wheaties box! Oh!
幸好你戴了套
Thank God you're wearing a condom.
是啊
I know, 'cause, boy,
我可不想让你怀孕啊 是不？
we wouldn't want to get you pregnant, right?
是啊 我都没在吃避孕药 而且我还在排卵期
I know. I'm not even taking any birth control and I'm ovulating.
我给你说过上次闯进我家来的双胞胎吗？
Did I tell you that twins run in my family?
双胞胎？
Twins?
我姐姐还有六胞胎呢
My sister had sextuplets.
六胞…
Sextu...
讲真吗？我要吃颗事后薄荷糖
Oh, really? Let me just get an after-sex mint.
来 汉娜
Here, Hannah, here.
你也吃一颗吧
Have one of these. Here you go.
乖
Yeah.
- 呃 味道好奇怪  - 咽下去了吗？
- Ugh! It tastes weird. - All done?
啊
Ah!
好妹子 嘘
Good girl. Phew!
那我们开始吧 斯蒂尔小姐？
Shall we begin, Ms. Steale?
第一页 第一段
Page one, paragraph one.
这必须要改
This must change!
你一开头就打错字了大哥
There's a typo in the header.
就这个？
That's it?
布莱克先生 你这态度老娘就不和你谈了
Mr. Black, I will end this negotiation right now!
对不起
My apologies.
第四页 十三到二十条
Page four, section 13-20.
拳X菊花…
With regards to anal fisting...
- 这有问题吗？ - 当然没有
- Is there a problem? - Absolutely not.
加上拳X阴道
And strike out vaginal fisting.
我是说 如果你要爆菊
I mean, if you're gonna do anal,
那你肯定就会顺带X了阴道了
you're obviously gonna have vaginal fisting. I mean, it's a given.
哦 那当然 我这就…
Oh, for sure. I will put that...
我把这条加粗写上
I'm putting that in there in bold.
下一页 性玩具 “可否接受SM”
Next page, sex toys. "Are they acceptable to the submissive?"
假丁丁 行 菊花塞 也行
Dildos, I guess. Butt plugs, fine.
- 好耶  - 慢着慢着…
- Fuck yeah! - Whoa, whoa, whoa...
这种内容怎么能浑水摸鱼？
How did this slip through the cracks?
情趣夹夹是搞毛？
What's with the genital clamps?
不好意思 斯蒂尔小姐 我…
Sorry, Ms. Steale, I...
我没找到你说的…
I can't seem to find those in my...
因为你压根就没写进去
Because you forgot to put them in there.
小学生才犯的错啊 布莱克先生
Rookie move, Mr. Black.
我真蠢
Silly me.
我们说清楚 我不接受3P…
Let's be clear. I will not share you with another woman.
- 至少要4P或5P  - 7P
- I require at least two or three. - Five.
- 9P  - 好那就9P
- Seven. - Seven it is.
你无法偷工减料的 布莱克先生
You're not gonna shortchange me, Mr. Black.
你真会讨价还价啊 斯蒂尔小姐
You drive a hard bargain, Ms. Steale.
- 谢谢夸奖  - 告诉你 斯蒂尔小姐
- Thank you. - You know, Ms. Steale,
我很想操你操到下个月
I'd like to fuck you into the middle of next month.
傻逼 你连下一分钟
Silly. You couldn't fuck me
都操不到
into the middle of the next minute.
我把你操到另一个银河系去
I'll fuck you into a different galaxy.
你会感觉到“啊冥王星上好冷”
You'll be like, "Oh, shit, it's cold in Pluto!"
是么 好 那我就要在史蒂文・霍金的展览上操你
Yeah, well, I'm gonna fuck you at the Stephen Hawking exhibit.
然后我会把你屁股揉出时空裂痕
And I'm gonna ram your ass so hard that I cause a tear in the time-space continuum.
我要把你操过整个奴隶时期 然后你就自由了
I'll fuck you through slavery times, and you'll get your freedom papers.
[电影《回到未来》里的跑车]
是么 那我就租一辆德罗宁跑车 然后把你操回未来
Yeah, well, I'm gonna rent me a DeLorean and fuck you back to the future.
我要把你操到另一颗星球上 全是《黑衣人》里那种虫子的星球上
I'll fuck you into a whole 'nother planet, where that insect is from Men in Black.
你就会感觉“哦卧槽 你操了我多少次？”
You'll be like, "Oh, shit! How many times you fuck me?"
七亿四千六百万次
Three million, 746 hundred million times.
然后你会问“为啥啊？”
And you'd be like, "Why?"
[电影《黑衣人》里两位主角的常用手段]
我就会说“闭嘴” 然后消除你的记忆
And I'd be like, "Shut up," and I hit you with the neuron, like...
你就会说
You'd be like,
“老天为啥我的阴道这么痛？”
"Oh, my God, why is my vagina so sore?"
我就会回答“大概是你摔倒了吧”
And I'd be like, "You fell."
说得好 布莱克先生
Well played, Mr. Black.
讲真 我以前真的这么干过
I've done this before.
他是我们大学的一位主要捐赠人
And he's a major beneficiary of our university.
有趣的是 他捐的都是现金
Interestingly enough, he donates all cash.
一块 五块 二十块
Usually in ones, fives, twenties,
偶尔捐来皱皱的一百块上面还有奇怪的粉粉
the odd rolled-up $100 bill that's got a little bit of powder on it.
请欢迎 克里斯蒂安・布莱克先生
Please welcome Mr. Christian Black.
你刚才乱说什么呢 关你屁事？
What you talkin' 'bout my business, huh? Don't get cut.
谢谢你 现在我们来说说人生和人生的目标
Thank you. Let's talk about life and your purpose.
你们在这个学校 都为了文凭而奋斗了四年
You all spent four hard years in this school getting your diploma,
你们让你们的父母欠债
putting your parents in debt,
是为了什么？
for what?
在全球变暖和经济崩溃的边缘
Between global warming and the world economy crashing,
我都不知道 你们这么努力的让自己变好是为了什么
I don't even know why you're trying to better yourselves.
放弃希望吧
Give up hope! Think about it.
你们都在浪费时间
You are wasting time.
你 你就是个瘾君子
You. You're a drug addict waiting to happen.
瞧瞧你 你现在迫不及待想出去抽根大麻
Look at you. You can't wait to get outta here and smoke some weed.
你 你是脱衣舞者
And you! You are a stripper!
不管我在说话还是坐着 你屁股都在扭
Your ass is twerkin' as I'm sitting here talking.
你能从任何事物里找到节奏
You can find the rhythm in anything.
还有你 先生
And you, sir.
哦 你是白人 哦那你就没事的
Well, you're white. You'll be fine.
所以 我其实想说
So, in closing, I would like to say,
“感谢上天我不是你们”
"Thank God I'm not you."
- 卡提莎 我的天 我们做到了  - 妹子
- Kateesha! Oh, my God, we did it! - Girl!
我太为你骄傲了
I'm so proud of you.
我该找谁说呢？就差一点了妹子
Who you telling? I was close, girl.
我再多给别人撸一管 就能当上优等生了呢
I was one handjob away from losing valedictorian to that bitch,
林赛・黄 是吧？
Lindsey Hung, right?
- 你在说什…  - 闭嘴
- What are you talking... - Shut up.
我看那碧池啊 满嘴胡话
I see that bitch, she talkin' shit.
待老娘教训了她
She gonna need a gynecologist
她就得去看妇科医生了
when I'm done fucking that bitch up! All right!
妹子 待会儿见了
Girl, I'll see you later.
老娘要去喂那碧池吃拳头
I'mma go punch a bitch in the throat.
林赛 你个双语系的碧池
Lindsey! You bilingual bitch!
真为你自豪
So proud of you.
汉娜
Hannah!
老爸
Dad!
见到你我好高兴
I'm so happy to see you.
哦 我真为你自豪
Oh! I'm so proud of you.
告诉你 我以为你会越长越难丑
You know, I thought you'd turn out not to be shit.
结果相比起以前那个喝醉的鸡样
But you ended up looking real good,
你现在还算能看
being that you from a drunken whore.
- 哦是啊  - 恩 你妈妈又去康复中心了
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah, your mama's over at the rehab.
二十七次了 真他妈着了魔
Twenty-seven times is the fucking charm.
- 是吗？ - 是啊我操
- Isn't it? - Yeah, it's the fucking charm.
嘿 我其他几位继父呢？
Hey, where are my other stepdads?
就在那里
Right over there.
老强尼 逼逼金
Jonny Quest, B. B. King.
至于那没穿衣服的老黑是谁我也不认识
I don't know who that nigga is with his shirt off.
大概是你亲生爹吧
That must be your birth daddy.
很不错 很不错的一群家伙
Yeah, it's all good. What a great bunch of guys.
就像老话说的“能凑出一个村儿”
And you know the old saying, "It takes a village."
确实是这样 尤其因为你妈
And it's true. Especially when it comes
还是个阴沟站街女
to your mom being a gutter slut
这村儿还是个乱交村
and the village is a gangbang.
- 乱交村  - 汉娜
- The village is a gangbang. - Hannah!
你好啊
Hi!
喂喂喂慢着 花花公子
Hey, hey, hey, hold up, player!
操 你走过来就亲我养大的姑娘？
Shit, how you gonna walk up and kiss the girl that I raised?
这他妈算什么事？
What kind of shit is this?
罗恩 这是我男朋友 克里斯蒂安・布莱克
Ron, this is my boyfriend, Christian Black.
男朋友
Boyfriend!
罗恩 我跟你说实话 我就操了她几次而已
Ron, to be honest with you, I just fucked her a few times.
“男朋友”这叫法 太严肃辣
"Boyfriend" makes it sound serious, like I went raw.
我是说 我可能…
I mean, I might've dipped, but...
你想娶了她？
Are you thinkin' about marrying her?
没
No.
那如果她怀孕了呢？
What if she get pregnant?
还是不娶 死都不娶
Still no, but hell no.
我喜欢这小伙
I like this fella!
我喜欢你这小黑鬼
I like this nigga right here.
我跟你继父扯得来
I fucks with your stepdad.
你知道不 咱俩都是花花公子 我喜欢你 哥们
You know what, from player to player, Black, I really like you, man.
- 你想操谁就去操谁  - 谢谢你
- You can fuck anybody you wanna fuck. - Thank you.
恩 但是别把她操完就扔 像我们对她妈妈那样
Yeah, just don't pass her around like we did her mama.
- 我就这点要求  - 没问题先生
- That's all I ask you to do. - Yes, sir, out of respect.
我们把她妈扔了 扔的可随便了呢
We passed her mama around like a baton, man.
是啊
Yeah.
你从来都没和我说过你妈啊
You never told me that about your mother.
你妈当时操遍了整个邻居街坊
Your mother fucked everybody in the neighborhood,
然后她突然想结婚成家了 来找我 我也就答应了
and then wanted to settle down with me, and I went for it.
告诉你 我得多和你出去玩 老哥
You know what, I gotta hang out with you, man,
偷点儿你的知识来 因为你真的很渊博
get your knowledge, man, 'cause you got a lot of wisdom.
哥渊博是因为哥经历得多
I got a lot of wisdom and I been through a lot,
哥骑过无数女人
and I done been with a lot of hos
哥手指上遗留下来的味道
and the smells that's on my fingers
- 都这么多年了…  - 哎呀我操
- over all the years... - Oh, shit! What!
- 味道还在 一直都在  - 我操
- Still there. Never went away. - Oh! Damn!
哇 先生 我能闻到每一个女人的味道
Wow, sir! I smelled every last single one of them!
一点儿不错 小兄弟
Yes, man.
感觉美丽与恐怖集于一体
It was like beautiful and horrible at the same time.
我这手爆过这世界上
I've stuck my hands in some of
最污的女人
the nastiest bitches' pants all over the world.
讲真？
Really?
- 亚洲的 马来西亚 刚果  - 恩
- Asia, Malaysia, Congo. - Hmm.
这是来自迪拜哒
That's Dubai right there.
我操 我闻到她X毛的味道了
Wow, I smell the hair.
我在迪拜机场爆了她菊花
Touched a bitch's booty hole in Dubai at the airport.
我觉得你能传授给我不少东西 老黑
I bet you could probably spit a lot of game to me, my nigga.
来照张相吧 咱俩照张相 自拍
Let's take a picture, let me get a picture of me and you. Make it a selfie.
不不宝贝儿 就我和他照
No, no, baby. Just me and him.
准备好了吗？一 二 三 尼哥
Ready? One, two, three. Nigga!
我们要去哪？
Where are we going?
恭喜毕业 汉娜
Congratulations, Hannah.
是辆车啊
That's a car.
车窗坏了的车？
With a broken window?
喜欢不？
Do you like it?
恩 挺好
Yeah. It's nice.
你知道我为了偷这辆车花了多大功夫么？
You know what I went through to steal this car?
我是说…这车是偷来的
I mean...The car was a steal.
- 你跟我翻白眼？ - 没
- Did you just roll your eyes at me? - No.
听好 这世上我只讨厌两件事
Listen, there's only two things I hate,
翻白眼和越梅干
when you roll your eyes at me and Craisins.
越梅干是什么？不算越梅 也不算果干
Like, what is a Craisin? It's not a cranberry, it's not a raisin.
这根本就说不通嘛
Like, it doesn't even make sense.
- 你丫有跟我翻白眼  - 我没有啊
- You just rolled your eyes at me again! - No, I didn't.
当然有 我都录下来了
Yes, you did. I have it on tape.
来看看
Check this out. Look at this.
瞧她在干嘛 翻白眼啊 快看
Oh, what's she doing? She's rolling her eye. Look at that.
- 你怎么做到的？ - 你 跟我走
- How did you do that? - Come on, you, with me, now.
但是…
But...
我来告诉你翻白眼的下场
Teach you a little lesson about rolling your eyes. Come on.
哦
Oh.
现在 你知道我为什么要惩罚你吗？
Now, do you know why I'm gonna punish you?
因为你是个喜欢虐待女人的变态
Because you're a sicko who likes abusing women.
你说的还有点道理 但是这并不是原因
While there may be some truth to that, that's not the reason.
因为我翻白眼了
Because I rolled my eyes.
对咯
Bingo.
哦
Oh!
等会儿你的屁股会比我的手要疼很多
This is gonna hurt you a whole lot more than it's gonna hurt me.
嘿
Ha!
欢迎来到我的世界
Welcome to my world.
哦 我操
Oh, God! Fuck!
好疼好疼
Ooh, that hurt! Oh!
你打了吗？
Did you do it?
嗷
Ow.
好 第十五行 该填“冬日饮品”
Okay, 15 across, "winter beverage."
妈的 你一点感觉都没？
Nothing? You don't feel nothing?
我真心喜欢织东西
I love knitting.
你到底要不要打我？我都开始无聊了
Are you gonna spank me? All this build-up is getting boring.
好吧好吧 跟老子玩？
Okay, okay, you wanna play?
老子有备而来
Oh, I got something for you.
让一下
Excuse me.
玩够了 现在准备好面对疾风吧
Enough of your games. It's about to get real dark in here.
欧
Sure.
你能不能找点有用的东西来啊？
Are you gonna find something that actually works?
光 明 大 老 哥
Big brother almighty!
哇哦
Whoo!
那是我女生联谊会里的拍子啊
That was my sorority paddle!
呃
Oh!
汉娜 你知道
You know, Hannah,
我并不想对你这么做
I didn't wanna have to do this to you,
但你丫太调皮了
but you've been a naughty girl.
你他妈把我的凳子打坏了？
Did you break my fucking stool?
没
No.
我觉得我挺擅长玩儿这个的
I think I'm pretty good at this.
哦…
Oh...
我不…我不明白
I don't...I don't understand.
我他妈什么都用上了 怎么就是没用
I fucking hit you with everything. I don't get it.
别自责
Don't feel bad.
自从我屁股移植后 我就从没有过啥感觉了
I haven't really felt anything down there since I got my butt implants.
明天…明天在我家见吧
I'll just... I'll see you back at my place tomorrow. Yeah.
你在这间房里 就得乖乖听我的命令
When you're in this room, you do as I say.
- 明白吗？ - 明白
- Is that understood? - Yes.
- 明白？ - 明白了 先生
- Yes, who? - Yes, sir.
好姑娘
Good girl.
举起手
Hands up.
转过去 跪下
Turn around. On your knees.
就这么别动
Stay.
别看我
Don't look at me!
手举起来
Raise your hand.
疼吗？
Did that hurt?
不疼
No.
有时 疼的感觉在心里
Sometimes the pain is in your mind.
唉呀妈呀我操你妈
God damn it! Motherfuck!
而有时疼的感觉不在心里
And sometimes the pain is not in your mind!
混球
Jerk!
我要问你一个十分重要的问题 斯蒂尔小姐
I have a very important question to ask you, Ms. Steale.
- 本・拉登在哪？ - 啥？
- Where is bin Laden? - What?
本・拉登在哪里？你最后一次见他是什么时候？
Where is bin Laden? When was the last time you saw bin Laden?
他在哪？
Where is he?
我不知道啊
I don't know!
他都死了五年了
He's been dead for five years!
老子从来不看这些时事新闻
I don't keep up on current events!
现在 折磨开始
And now the real torture begins.
我们刚才读到哪儿了？
Where were we?
我忘掉安全口令了啊
I can't remember the safe word.
二十三章
Chapter 23.
“西雅图的今天十分阴冷”
"It was a cold, gloomy day in Seattle."
老天 这书真是五十度操蛋
Oh, God, this book is 50 shades of fucking terrible.
谁写的啊 三年级小学生？
Who wrote this, a third-grader?
我们回去玩儿水刑吧
Please go back to the water-torture thing!
- 安全口令是什么？ - 停下啦
- What's the safe word? - Stop it!
你的安全口令是什么？
What's your safe word?
我不知道啊
I don't know.
拜托…能不能放我下来？
Please just...Are you gonna let me down now?
行 斯蒂尔小姐
Yes, Ms. Steale.
我先找下钥匙
If I could just find these keys.
你没看到钥匙吗…别 我知道钥匙在哪 只是…
You didn't see the keys...No, I know where they are. I just...
老天 我的胳膊开始痛了
God, my arms are really starting to hurt.
我有个办法
I got an idea.
瞧 大多数人在自己的XX房间里都用万向锁
See, most people use a universal lock key in their sex dungeons...
就是为了避免这种事发生  - 嗯哼
-For reasons just like this. -Hmm.
但是你这个是个多重模组的旋钮锁
But what you got here is an over-molded swivel key.
这可是定制的
All right, that's a custom job.
你得找别的专家来看看了
You're gonna need somebody else to take a look at this.
好吧 我也不好说
Yeah, I don't know what to tell you.
下次我会在你的钥匙上放跟踪器一类的东西 以免你弄丢
Next time, I'd put one of those tracker app things on the key so you don't lose it.
- 叫什么来着？ - 我知道
- What are they called? - Oh, I know the name.
这名字在嘴边却说不出来 T字母开头
It's on the tip of my tongue. It starts with a "T."
- 塔…  - 还是腾？
- Ta... - Maybe Ten?
心灵感应？
Telepathy?
[IOS上一款专门定位随身物品的APP]
喂 傻逼们 那个叫瓦片
Hey, dipshits, it's called a Tile.
瓦片
Tile!
我操 牛逼啊
Holy shit, you're good!
- 不愧上过大学  - 一点儿没错
- You went to college! - Hell yeah!
拜托
Come on!
我这辈子撬过无数锁 但从来没见过这样的
I've picked a lot of locks in my day, but I've never seen anything like this.
- 哥们 锁子很厉害  - 谢谢你
- Man, it's impressive. - Thank you.
哎 我没办法 下一个谁来？
Yeah. I got nothing. Who's next?
下一个谁来？搞毛？十一罗汉吗？
Who's next? What are you guys, Ocean's Eleven?
你要叫多少潘抗来？
How many more fuckups are you gonna bring in here?
- 退后  - 呃
- Stand back! - Oh.
数到三 大魔术师
On the count of three, the Great Mysterio
就能解开这些锁
shall command these shackles unlocked!
一 注意看好了
One! Do not divert your gaze.
二 幻象
Two! Illusion!
三 大秘术
Three! Mysterio!
- 谢谢你  - 呃…
- Thank you. - Um...
呃…
Uh...
没用啊 锁子还都在
Yeah, that didn't work. All the locks are still there.
啥都没发生
Nothing happened!
欧 那我没办法了
Oh. I got nothing, guys.
老天
Jesus Christ.
说道消失 我一小时后有一场犹太成人礼要表演 大秘书
Oh, speaking of disappearing, I have a bar mitzvah in one hour. Mysterio!
- 哦卧槽  - 老天
- Oh, damn! - Oh, my God.
你的契约里可没写这个
This was not in the contract!
我们要去哪？
Where we going?
去我爸妈家里 吃完饭
To my parents' house for dinner.
- 你看起来真美  - 谢谢你
- You look lovely. - Thank you.
你在哪学会的跳舞？
Where'd you learn to dance?
在坦帕市的一个小俱乐部
At this little club in Tampa.
舞起来
Dance!
耶
Yeah!
哦 哇
Ooh, wow.
啊我操
Ah! Fuck!
这啥啊？
What's that?
老天 他鸡鸡比婴儿都小
Oh, my God, he's got a baby dick!
是光线问题 光线不好 有阴影
It's just the lighting! It's bad lighting! It's creating shadow!
他不小 你们这群小人
It's not little! You're just little people!
嗨
Hi.
啊 你来了
Oh, you made it.
汉娜 见到你真高兴
Hannah! It's so good to see you.
你好
Hi.
汉娜 这是我老爸 加里
Hannah, this is my dad, Gary.
见到你我们真是非常开心 汉娜
Are we ever happy to meet you, Hannah.
- 真的？ - 当然
- Really? - Oh, yes.
我以前几乎都确信克里斯蒂安是基佬了
I was sure that Christian was gay.
他讲卫生 还喜欢雷迪嘎嘎
He's well-groomed, loves Lady Gaga.
[CNN金牌主播]
一看到安德森・库伯眼睛就发直
Can't take his eyes off of Anderson Cooper.
共和党员怎么能看CNN呢？
What kind of Republican watches CNN?
嗨 我是梅
Hi! I'm Mai!
见到你真好
It's so nice to meet you!
不敢相信你居然是共和党
I can't believe you're a Republican.
那是他深藏内心的秘密
That's his deep, dark secret.
来吧？
Shall we?
- 还是不敢相信你是共和党  - 对不起辣
- I can't believe you're a Republican. - Sorry.
啊…
Ah...
布莱克夫人 这饭菜看起来棒极了
Mrs. Black, this food looks amazing.
哦 谢谢你 汉娜
Oh, thank you, Hannah.
对我们而言
Well, it was important to me
我们的养子能够接受自己传统文化的熏陶 是很重要的
that our adopted children were exposed to their native cultures.
所以 伊莱 我给你准备了巴兰古
So, for Eli, I have prepared Balangu.
是尼日利亚做法的辣羊肉
It's a spicy goat dish from Nigeria.
梅 我们为你准备了北京烤鸭
And for Mai, of course, we have Peking Duck
来自中国大陆的传统
from the Mandarin province of China.
可我是韩国人
I'm Korean!
别瞎说 梅
Don't be fresh, Mai!
数十亿的中国小孩
There are billions of starving Chinese children
正在饿着肚子给耐克做鞋子
who need their energy to make sneakers for Nike,
他们要是能吃上这一顿命都可以不要
and they would kill for this meal.
对于克里斯蒂安 炸鸡和酷爱饮料
For Christian, of course, we have fried chicken and Kool-Aid.
在密歇根的底特律城十分受欢迎
It's a very popular dish in Detroit, Michigan.
还有你最爱的辣酱
And your favorite, of course, hot sauce!
哎呀老妈
Oh, Mom.
那么 汉娜 你们俩有兴趣要孩子么？
So, Hannah, are you interested in having children?
恩 只要是对的人就行
Yes, I would, if I met the right person.
哦 你们不知道如果能抱上孙子我们得有多开心
Oh, you have no idea what joy we have had from having our kids.
梅是我最担心的
Mai's the one that I worried about the most.
她那么可爱
I mean, she was so sweet.
我是说 她某天几乎可以肯定会和加里私奔
I mean, it seemed almost inevitable that she'd grow up one day and run off with Gary.
就像以前那个小导演
Like that little director fellow, you know,
最后嫁给了米娅・法洛的那个？
the one that married Mia Farrow?
亲爱的 别说了 她是我们的女儿啊
Oh, sweetheart, please stop. She's our daughter.
不过她确实性感
She's a hot little number, though.
汉娜 我真心推荐
Hannah, I would really recommend
你们去领养贫困儿童
adopting underprivileged children.
你能这么说真好 布莱克夫人
Wow, that's really just so sweet of you, Mrs. Black.
在慈善晚会上这会是很好的话题
It is a great conversation starter at charities,
帮助你建立政治立场
it helps your social standing...
给我
Give it to me.
[太阳马戏团：加拿大著名马戏团]
…你的阴道也不会松弛到像太阳马戏团的演员那样
...and your vag doesn't get stretched out
like an elastic band at Cirque du Soleil.
好了老妈 别说了
Okay, Mom. Mom, please.
我为了我的孩子什么都愿意做
There was just nothing I wouldn't do for my children.
我甚至为了梅而学会了普通话
I even learned to speak Mandarin for Mai.
这他妈算是语言吗
That's not even a real language.
捅到底
Hit that bottom!
汉娜 你家是哪里的？
Hannah, where is your family from?
哦…
Oh...
我妈妈住在乔治亚
My mom lives in Georgia.
哦 亚特兰大啊
Oh, Atlanta!
哦 那你母亲一定是位脱衣舞者了
Oh, then your mom must be a stripper.
她其实住在萨凡纳辣
She actually lives in Savannah,
而且只是个家庭主妇
and she's just a housewife.
我信我信
Sure she is, dear.
我过几天其实就要去看她
I'm gonna go and visit her, actually, in a few days.
还有人要喝点酒吗？
Drinks anyone? Drinkies?
- 我要两杯  - 我也想要 老妈
- I'll have two. - I'd love to, Mom,
但是我之前答应过汉娜 要给她看看咱们的房子
but I promised Hannah I'd show her the estate.
在“家”搞 爽
"Home stretch"! Yes!
失陪了
Excuse us, please.
去“买杂货”辣
It's "grocery time".
我感觉飞天啊
It's like I'm on air right now!
你怎么从来没跟我提过她
How come you didn't tell me about her?
谁 我老妈？
Who, my mom?
老天 还有昵称？
My God, she has a nickname?
你爱她吗？
Do you love her?
当然 她是我妈啊
Of course, she's my mother.
老天 你爱她多久了？
God, how long has this been going on?
从出生开始
Since birth.
喂 拜托 我可比不过她
Oh, come on, I can't compete with that!
喂 你又不用和她比
Hey, you don't have to compete with it!
你是我男友 她是我妈
You're my boyfriend, she's my mom.
两种完全不同的感情啊好吗
They're two totally different relationships!
不 不是的 汉娜 你是我的 明白不？
No, they're not! Okay, Hannah, you're mine, okay?
不能有妈妈 不能有兄弟姐妹
There's no mother, no brother, no cousins, no second cousin removed,
不能有父母关系好的好朋友们
no friends that you call cousin 'cause your parents are close!
- 都不能有  - 连好朋友都不能有？
- There's none of that. - No play cousins?
不能
No play cousins.
克里斯蒂安 你想做甚啊？
Christian, what do you want?
[凯文・哈特：美国演员、编剧，以电影高产著称]
我不想看凯文・哈特的脸出现在每一部电影里
I want Kevin Hart not to be in every movie!
为什么？他那么有趣的
Why? He's hilarious.
拜托 还有别的黑人演员
Come on, there's other black actors!
- 他们怎么样？ - 谁？
- How about them? - Like who?
[二一四年喜剧电影]
可以是《佐州自救兄弟》里的山姆・杰克逊
It could've been Sam Jackson in Ride Along.
谁知道他这次会戴什么样的傻逼假发？
Who knows what kind of crazy wig he would have been wearing?
我以为你想要我
I thought you wanted me!
那你又想要什么？情书？
What do you want, love letters?
[爱蒂宝：美国销售新鲜水果花束的公司]
- 吻痕？爱蒂宝的果篮？ - 恩
- Hickies? Edible Arrangements? - Mmm.
[美国文化中，花篮是送给爱人，而果篮是赠送给亲友的]
他们卖的都不是真花 你他妈还想要果篮
You know, that's not even real flowers. It's fucking fruit.
是啊 但是很好吃啊
Yeah, but it's delicious.
这只是开始 好吗？
And it's a start, okay?
继续发展下去 就是蒂凡尼牌订婚戒
And maybe we could advance to a Tiffany's engagement ring,
和一个邀请五百位亲朋好友的婚礼
and a wedding where we invite 500 of our closest friends,
甚至生上七个娃 住在一个大豪宅里
and then we have seven kids, and we live in a big house...
哇 你真是计划的好啊 是不？
Whoa. You had this whole thing planned out, huh?
卧槽 只有我觉得很热么？
You know, is it me or is it hot in here? Shit.
你想让我变成一个我不是的人
You want me to be somebody that I'm not.
不不不 不是我在改变你
No, no, it's not me that's changing you.
是你在改变我
It's you that's changing me!
等等
Wait a minute.
[二三年美国电影]
那是电影《真情电波》里的台词
That's a line from the movie Radio.
不是啊
No, it's not.
就是啊 小库伯・戈丁参演的那部
Yeah, yeah, the movie with Cuba Gooding, Jr.,
他演了个智障运动员
where he played this mentally disabled athlete.
[Radio是电影里主角的绰号]
“不是我们在教Radio”
"It's not us that's teaching Radio,
“而是Radio在教我们”
"it's Radio that's teaching us."
不不不 我说的可不一样
Nah, mine is way different.
差不多啊
It's the same premise.
你想跟我斗？
You complete me?
[一九九六年美国电影]
这句又是出自《甜心先生》同样是小库伯・戈丁主演
Jerry Maguire, also starring Cuba Gooding, Jr.
我不明白你怎么对他那么痴迷
I don't understand your whole fixation on him.
告诉你 一直以来我都以为自己没有找到合适自己的出路
You know, all this time I thought I wasn't in the right place,
但其实我找到了
but I was!
[二二年美国电影]
那出自《冰狗任务》
That's Snow Dogs.
操
God damn it!
[美国在线影片租赁商]
我不能再看Netflix了
I gotta stop binging on Netflix.
汉娜
Hannah!
听起来很悲伤啊
That song sounds so sad.
[美国灵魂音乐创作歌手]
不如卢瑟・范德鲁斯的《与父亲共舞》悲伤
Not as sad as Luther Vandross' Dance With My Father.
老天 我听那歌都哭死了
Oh, God, that song tears me up.
[恶搞电影中黑人自幼丧父梗]
每次我听 我都想问“我父亲去哪儿了？”
Every time I hear it, I just wanna go, "Where's my daddy?"
克里斯蒂安 我们得谈谈
Christian, we have to talk.
像白人那样谈谈？
You mean like white people?
有什么问题吗？
What's wrong with that?
也没 白人老是话很多 你造不？
Well, they just talk a lot, you know?
他们和黑人不一样
They do it differently than black people do it.
他们不吵架 他们讨论
White people don't like to argue, they like to discuss.
一讨论就开始扯那些高考词汇
Then they start throwing around all these big SAT words
然后在心理让对方感觉愧疚
and putting a lot of emotional guilt on each other.
太多心机辣
It's just too much to deal with.
我还是喜欢黑人的方式 你懂不 就互相骂
I like it the black way, you know, where we curse each other out,
有可能还要打架 打完还是好朋友
we may fight, and then we get cool again,
但是我们在背后捅刀子 就像
but we talk about each other behind each other's back, like,
“老子才不理那个小婊咂”
"Oh, nah, I ain't fucking with that bitch."
但尼不会…
But what you not gonna do...
- 但尼不会… - 尼会…
- But what you not gonna do... - You not gonna do...
- 尼不要否认老子  - 呃不
- You not about to "not" me! - Uh-uh...
别让老子拍起手来啊大兄弟
Don't let me get to clappin', boo.
欧快滚
Oh, hell no.
瞧 这才叫…沟通
See, that's... That's communication.
我已经感觉好些了
I feel better already.
- 克里斯蒂安  - 干嘛
- Christian. - Hey!
你不会因为我还没签你那个契约
You're not upset because I haven't signed
而生气吧？
the contract yet, are you?
我是说 你那契约在法律上压根无效 你明白吧？
I mean, it's not even legally enforceable. You know that, right?
重要的是 我有我的规矩
What's important here are the rules.
而如果你打破了我的规矩 你就要受到惩罚
And if you break them, you should be punished.
你要怎么惩罚我？
How are you gonna punish me?
第一 被禁足
First off, you'll get grounded.
我会让你在墙角面壁一小时
I'll make you stand in the corner for an hour.
然后赶回你自己的房间
And then I will send you to your room
不给你吃晚饭 小妹妹
without no supper, young lady.
克里斯蒂安 这真是疯了 你为啥一定要惩罚我？
Christian, this is crazy. Why do you need to punish me?
因为老子是五十一度操蛋
Because I'm 51 shades of fucked up!
你知道我性格就像个野人
You know I'm five-four seconds from wildin'.
手头事多的一逼
I got three fillets for fryin'.
本来有九十九件事要做 但是现在女人也成问题了
I got 99 problems, but now a bitch is one!
这就是一百件麻烦事 汉娜
That's 100 problems, Hannah!
我对付不了那么多 九十九件事还好
I can only deal with so much. 99's fine.
一百件事…我还不能数到一百呢
A hundred jus...I can't even count that far.
好吧
Okay.
然后你就给我甩脸子
Then you show me the worst.
来啊 老娘就试试你能怎么甩
I wanna see how bad it can get.
从今往后
No more of this pussy-ass punishment
老娘不会再接受你儿戏一般惩罚了
you've been doling out thus far.
老娘要玩就玩到底
I wanna go all the way.
你能行么？
Is that something that you think you can do?
谢谢老天
Thank you.
行
Yes.
弯腰
Bend over.
恩
Hmm.
嗯嗯
Mmm-mmm.
恩
Hmm.
啊哈
Aha.
“老乔”是最好的鞭子
Nothin' says ass-whuppin' like good ol' Joe Jackson.
汉娜…
Hannah...
我要抽你六次
I'm gonna spank you six times.
我要你和我一起数
I need you to count with me.
啊老天 操你妈的
God damn it, motherfucker!
我说和我一起数
I said count with me!
一 二
One! Two!
天啊 疼死了 我记不清数哪里了
Jesus! It hurts so bad I can't keep count! Where were we?
我也不知道
I don't know!
老天啊 汉娜
God damn it, Hannah!
我不会数数 明白不？
I don't know how to count, okay?
我那瘾君子老妈从不教我
My crackhead mother never taught me.
这样吧？我们试试西班牙语
How about this? Let's try in Spanish.
- 西班牙语？ - [西语]是
- Spanish? - Si.
[西语]三 四
Tres. Cuatro.
我不太清楚 但我记得三后面是五啊
I'm not too sure, but I think cinco comes after tres.
你在逗老娘吧？三后面是四
Are you kidding me? Cuatro comes after tres.
好吧 别生我气啊 我又不会说西班牙语
Well, don't get mad at me. I don't know Spanish.
我那瘾君子老妈从来没教过我怎么数数 也没教过我西班牙语
Look, my crackhead mother never taught me how to count or how to speak Spanish.
- 现在我们又得从头开始  - 别啊
- Now we gotta start from scratch! - No!
哇哦
Whoo!
累死了 妈的 真累人
I am tired. Oh, God, that is exhausting.
我估计明天要浑身酸痛
Oh, I'm gonna be sore tomorrow.
好了 来吧 起来
Oh. Come on, let's get you up.
别碰我
Don't touch me!
嘿
Hey!
你看见我这样 高兴么？
Does it make you happy to see me like this?
[《指环王》里的小妖精]
不太高兴 你看起来就像是伤心的咕噜
I mean, not really. You look like a sad Gollum.
弓腰驼背的哭 看起来还有点疯
Like you's all bent over, and you're crying. You look a little crazy.
拜托 别恨我啊
Come on, don't hate me.
恨你？
Hate you?
我厌恶你
I loathe you.
哇 这词我得查词典了
Whoa. That's a thesaurus word right there.
我就像黑人恨警察那样恨你
I hate you the way black people hate cops.
哇
Wow.
我就像共和党恨奥巴马医保那样恨你
I hate you the way Republicans hate ObamaCare!
宝贝儿 拜托
Baby, come on now.
我就像侃爷恨所有人那样恨你
I hate you the way Kanye West hates everybody else!
恩 我其实觉得他吐槽霉霉还吐的挺对
Well, I'm kind of with him on Taylor Swift.
那婊咂都唱的什么玩意儿啊？
What is that bitch singing about?
你再也不许这样打我了
You will never do that to me again.
你不是说没关系的嘛
You said it was cool.
我认识的黑鬼老司机
I know niggas, grimy niggas who do not value themselves,
会毫不犹豫的冲下来
and they will have no problem coming down here
爆X你的菊花
to fuck your little ass up!
- 哟 慢着慢着  - 只要一声令下
- Whoa. Slow it up now. - Just one "Cuckoo!"
他们就会朝你冲锋
And they will swoop down on you
就像鸽子吃面包那样
like pigeons on old garlic bread!
你不能对他们下令
You can't be cuckooin' on this mo'fuck!
你得让他们冷静
You gotta calm them niggas down.
你造不？
You know what?
我们来试试别的吧
Let's try something else.
哎哟喂 真可爱 角色扮演呐
Aw, this is cute. I get it, a little role-play.
真可爱
It's cute.
小手铐 哎哟哟
Handcuffs. All right.
你还想着抽我？
You thought you were gonna do this shit to me?
你惹错了女人
You messed with the wrong bitch.
你听起来好生气啊
You sound angry.
[《被解救的姜戈》中的黑奴女人]
这一下是为了《被解救的迪姜戈》里的凯里・华盛顿
This is for Kerry Washington from De-jango Unchained!
我操…是“姜戈” 迪不发音
It's fucking...That is Django! The "D" is silent!
[《为奴十二载》中的黑奴女人]
这一下是为了《为奴十二载》里的露皮塔・尼永奥
This is for Lupita Nyong'o in 12 Years a Slave!
我操 疼死了
God damn it! It stings so bad!
她只是想要几块肥皂
All she wanted was some soap!
抗菌肥皂
Even the antibacterial soap!
[美国黑人男演员]
这一下是为了丹泽尔・华盛顿
This is for Denzel Washington.
等等 他是个男的啊
Wait, he's not even a woman.
你都发疯了
You're just getting crazy.
[一九八九年美国电影]
但是他在《光荣》里哭了
But they made him cry in Glory.
谁能让丹泽尔・华盛顿流泪？谁都不行
Who makes Denzel Washington cry? Nobody!
像这样流泪吗？
You talkin' 'bout like this?
瞧 我留下一滴“光荣”泪
See, look, I have a Glory tear.
[电影《空前绝后满天飞》里转为黑人打造的飞机]
如果不是丹泽尔・华盛顿 现在我们还得做“灵魂梦飞翔”
If it wasn't for Denzel Washington, Flight would've been a fucking Soul Plane!
我操啊
Shit!
搞不懂他们为什么造灵魂梦飞翔号
Why the fuck did they make Soul Plane anyway?
这一下是为了《五十度灰》的女主
And this is for the little white girl in Fifty Shades of Grey!
她叫约翰逊 达科塔・约翰逊
Johnson. Dakota Johnson.
她在整部电影里都裸着被操啊
She had to be naked the whole fucking movie!
还他妈基本没有片酬可以拿
That shit was just gratuitous!
哇 哦啊
Whoo! Ah!
疼 疼 感觉就像…
It burns! It burns! It feels like someone lit a...
屁股着火啦 啊 疼
My ass on fire! Oh, God, it hurts!
结束辣？
We done?
哦 没有 小黑 我们还没完呢
Oh, no, nigga. No, we not finished yet!
还没完呢 小黑鬼
We not finished with you yet, nigga!
什么？你要作甚？
What? Where you goin' with this?
我要带你的屁股回到中世纪
I'm about to get medieval on your ass.
欢迎来到我的世界 傻逼玩意儿
Welcome to my world, motherfucker.
哦天啊
Oh, God!
好疼啊
This hurts so much.
我真想去死
I wish I'd died.
别碰 别碰
Don't touch it! Don't touch it!
啊 还在痒痒
Oh, it's tickling.
克里斯蒂安 我以为你会喜欢咧
Christian, I thought you'd like it.
那有什么好喜欢的
What's there to like!
哪种变态会打别人来取乐啊？
What kind of sick pervert beats you for their own enjoyment?
克里斯蒂安 你不会想和我这样的人在一起的
Christian, you don't want somebody like me.
你就是我想要的人
You're exactly what I want.
一个破产的 有着文学艺术文凭的大学生
A broke college graduate with a liberal arts degree
毫无前景可言
and no future prospects.
正是我想要的
It's exactly what I want.
克里斯蒂安 我已经无可救药的爱上你了
Christian, I've fallen head over heels in love with you.
呃…哇
Uh...Whoa!
慢着 这可不在协议里啊
Slow it up. That is not in the contract.
我还特意说了
Like, it specifically says, and I quote,
“臭婊子不要爱老黑”
"Bitch don't love a nigga."
明白？我还双倍加粗了这几个字
Okay? And I double-bolded that.
我就知道我应该逼你签字的
I knew I should have had you sign this contract.
克里斯蒂安 我觉得你最好离开吧
Christian, I think it'd be best if you leave.
滚
Get out!
好 你想要我走？行 我走
Fine, you want me to leave? You want me to leave? Fine, I will leave!
好吧？等等 暂停
Okay? Wait, time-out.
呃…
Um...
这是我家诶
I live here.
该走的不是你么？对不？
Shouldn't you be the one leaving? Am I wrong?
带把伞 因为…
Take an umbrella 'cause...
下雨辣 婊咂
Bitch, it's raining.
把我的车还我
I need my car back.
我已经卖掉了
I already sold that piece of shit.
卖了三十七块 我会写支票给你的
I'll send you a check for $37.
欧 比黄书都便宜呢
That is way below Blue Book!
汉娜
Hannah!
克里斯蒂安 你得放我走了
Christian, you have to let me go.
求你听我说
Please, listen to me!
不 你听我说
No, you listen to me.
你会找到这么个人的
You'll find someone. Somebody who wants to be open
一个愿意接受你那些下流玩意儿的人
to all the demeaning things that you wanna do to them.
汉娜
Hannah!
克里斯蒂安
Christian.
哦
Ooh.
啊
Ah!
天啊
God!
他怎么会爱你？他连自己都不爱
How is he gonna love you? He doesn't even love himself.
瞅瞅他那发型啊妹子
Did you see his haircut, girl?
你怎么会觉得这感情能发展下去呢？
How could you think this was gonna end well?
绝不反悔
Never look back.
克里斯蒂安
Christian.
汉娜
Hannah.
在我跑了四十七层楼梯的时间里
While running down 47 flights of stairs,
我想了很多事
I had plenty of time to think.
然后当我在二十三楼晕倒的时候 我意识到我该给你道个歉
And when I passed out on the 23rd floor, I realized I owed you an apology.
我就想说 我不该那么对你 对不起
I just want to say I'm sorry for the way I treated you.
尤其是那水刑
Especially for the whole waterboarding thing.
我觉得你对本・拉登的想法是对的
Turns out you were right about bin Laden.
- 谁知道那些呢？ - 所有人都知道
- Who knew? - Everyone.
恩？
Hmm?
你伤害了我 克里斯蒂安
You hurt me, Christian.
我知道 但是我还有软点的鞭子啊
I know. But I have softer whips.
上面还带粉色毛毛的那种
You know the kind with the pink fur on it?
那种打起来不疼
It takes the sting off.
我不是在说这个
That's not what I'm talking about.
- 你想要浪漫的爱情  - 那是我应得的
- You want romance. - I deserve it.
好 那你告诉我
Well, what's more romantic
还有比跑四十七层楼梯更浪漫的么？
than running down 47 flights of stairs?
我跑断了一根腿筋啊你造吗？
You know I pulled a hamstring?
你死了没？
Did you die?
没死 但是我至少一周不能去我的XX房了
No, but that's gonna keep me out of the Red Room for at least a week.
拜拜傻逼
Bye, bitch.
好吧好吧好吧 汉娜 等等 汉娜
Okay, okay, okay. Hannah, wait, wait. Hannah!
别 克里斯蒂安
No, Christian. You are incapable
我无法和你拥有一段平凡的爱情
of having a normal relationship.
我知道 但我正在努力尝试 好吗？
I know, but I'm trying, okay?
我也想像那个老年痴呆的老头一样
I want to be like that old man whose wife has Alzheimer's,
每天起来
and he wakes up every day
都能和他老婆一起唠人生
and he tells her the story about their lives together.
然后俩人一起睡一觉就再也不起来
And then they take a nap, but they don't wake up.
因为他们死翘翘辣
Because they're dead.
[二四年美国电影]
这又出自《恋恋笔记本》
That's The Notebook.
就是那部莱恩・高斯利和那个大脑门姑娘的电影？
That's the one with Ryan Gosling and the girl with the big-ass forehead?
哦
Oh.
他从来没忘记她
He never forgot her.
你又不喜欢斯派克斯的电影
You don't even like Nicholas Sparks movies.
我以前不喜欢 但现在喜欢啊
I used to hate them, but now I love 'em.
[之前提到麦莉・塞勒斯主演的爱情片]
包括《绝唱》
Even The Last Song.
那他妈为啥能拍成电影啊？
Why was that even a movie?
你知道原著都不能算是本小说么？
You know that wasn't even a book?
好吧 如果我再给你一次机会 我必须看到你的改变
Well, if I'm gonna give you another chance, things have to be different.
我明白
I know.
我有些很重要的事想告诉你
I have something very important I wanna tell you.
我爱…
I lo...
我…
I...
我想说的是
What I'm trying to say is, I love
我爱
Empire.
那库基说的最疯狂的事。
That Cookie just says the craziest things.
好吧
Okay.
我爱你
I love you.
我知道你爱我
I knew you loved me.
我有最后一个惊喜给你
I have one last surprise for you.
但是你得先收拾好行李
But you're gonna have to pack a bag.
你要带我去做私人飞机辣？
Are we gonna go on your private jet?
老天 啥样的飞机啊？
Oh, my God, what kind of jet is it?
别别别告诉我 惊喜我一下
No, no, no. Don't tell me. I want to be surprised.
啊
Ah!
我不敢相信你居然认为我会带你去坐私人飞机
I can't believe you thought I'd take you on a private jet.
我是爱你 但是你连戒指都没有诶
I love you and all, but you don't even have a ring yet.